<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Data><Series>
  <id>78846</id>
  <Actors>|David Threlfall|Anne-Marie Duff|Jody Latham|Chris Bisson|Dean Lennox Kelly|Maxine Peake|Elliot Tittensor|Rebecca Atkinson|Anthony Flanagan|Rebecca Ryan|Gerard Kearns|James McAvoy|Jack Deam|Joseph Furnace|Luke Tittensor|Maggie O'Neill|Marjorie Yates|Gillian Kearney|</Actors>
  <Airs_DayOfWeek>Tuesday</Airs_DayOfWeek>
  <Airs_Time>10:00 PM</Airs_Time>
  <ContentRating>TV-MA</ContentRating>
  <FirstAired>2004-01-13</FirstAired>
  <Genre>|Comedy|Drama|</Genre>
  <IMDB_ID>tt0377260</IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Network>Channel 4</Network>
  <NetworkID></NetworkID>
  <Overview>Blisteringly funny, offbeat drama following the rollercoaster lives and loves of an anarchic family from Manchester. Meet the Gallaghers. Mum went AWOL years ago, Dad stayed at home with the six children only to hit the bottle. And sometimes the kids... The real head of the family is big sister Fiona (20), who looks after Carl (11), Debbie (9) and baby Liam (3). She is occasionally helped, more often hindered, by reluctant virgin 'Lip' (16) and the actively gay, but very private, Ian (15).
 
Welcome to a hectic world of sexual adventures, triumphs, love, scams and a fair bit of crime on a rough Manchester housing estate, where wheel-less cars are the norm and the moving ones are stolen. </Overview>
  <Rating>9.2</Rating>
  <RatingCount>33</RatingCount>
  <Runtime>60</Runtime>
  <SeriesID>22545</SeriesID>
  <SeriesName>Shameless</SeriesName>
  <Status>Ended</Status>
  <added></added>
  <addedBy></addedBy>
  <banner>graphical/78846-g4.jpg</banner>
  <fanart>fanart/original/78846-4.jpg</fanart>
  <lastupdated>1430773769</lastupdated>
  <poster>posters/78846-1.jpg</poster>
  <tms_wanted_old>1</tms_wanted_old>
  <zap2it_id>EP00634967</zap2it_id>
</Series>
<Episode>
  <id>335091</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>1</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>0</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>|Jonny Campbell|</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Christmas Special 2004</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>1</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2004-12-23</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>It's Christmas on the Chattersworth Estate and it looks set to be a white Christmas as snow starts to fall but as always Christmas wouldn't be christmas without a disaster or two.
Veronica's mother, Carol, and her brother, Marty, turn up after Marty caught Carol in bed with his best mate and decided to burn the house down in revenge.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>0</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Paul Abbott|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <airsafter_season></airsafter_season>
  <airsbefore_episode>1</airsbefore_episode>
  <airsbefore_season>2</airsbefore_season>
  <filename>episodes/78846/335091.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1295026786</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>26300</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>296350</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>1</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>|Mark Mylod|</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Episode 1</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>1</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2004-01-13</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Fiona Gallagher struggles to raise her five younger siblings after her mother leaves and her father hits the bottle, but her life is changed by the arrival of wheeler-dealer Steve.
[Source: Radio Times]
On a night out with neighbor Veronica Fisher, Fiona Gallagher's bag is stolen and handsome stranger Steve McBride chases after the thief. While he isn't successful in capturing the thief, he does succeed in capturing the eye of Fiona, and she invites him home to not only engage in passionate sex but also to meet the rest of the Gallagher family. Lip Gallagher discovers a hidden folder full of gay magazines belonging to brother Ian Gallagher and attempts to &quot;test&quot; him with a trip to Karen Jackson's (whom has presently been giving Lip oral sex in exchange for tuition) house but things don't go according to plan when Karen's dad Eddie walks in and realizes whats going on. After chasing Lip and Ian away Eddie returns to collect his stuff and storms out leaving wife Sheila Jackson heart broken. Lip gets Karen's verdict on her earlier test on Ian and the results disappoint him. Steve attempts to win Fiona's heart with a new washing machine, but soon realizes she can't be bought. Lip is furious when he discovers his brother has been sleeping with a married man, who happens to have kids. Steve comes clean with Fiona about how he really earns his living after taking her out for a meal and finally wins her over. Lip has a heart to heart with Ian and accepts the fact that he's definitely gay. </Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.5</Rating>
  <RatingCount>22</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Paul Abbott|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/296350.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1387700151</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>15750</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>192</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>346</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>296351</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>2</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>|Jonny Campbell|</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Episode 2</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>2</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2004-01-20</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>La Disparition</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Frank finds him self in France with no idea of how he got there.
After Shelia's husband attacks Frank in the Pub over the incident with his daughter in the previous episode, involving Ian &amp; Lip, Frank returns home. He attacks Steve and Ian before disappearing back into the night. In revenge for the attack Steve dumps Frank in France.
It's Friday and Frank is missing. Fiona begins to worry as its Giro day and a full scale search is launched. When a body is found in the local canal the family fear the worst-but it's just a Police PR stunt. Fiona realises that Steve has dumped Frank in France and demands he gets Frank back. Veronica and Kev go with Steve to get cheap booze.
Frank returns safe and well and decides to make his move on Shelia! He moves in with her!</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>8.3</Rating>
  <RatingCount>12</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Paul Abbott|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/296351.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1387700167</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>15750</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>296352</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>3</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>|Jonny Campbell|</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Episode 3</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>3</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2004-01-27</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>The volcanic Gallagher family moves away from centre stage as Veronica and Kev become the centre of this episodes action. Kev accidentally proposes to a excited and delighted Veronica. But he's only proposing to rebuff the attention of a female customer at the Pub he occasionally works at.
However, a drunken Frank blabs to everyone. The wedding is planned and gaining pace and Kev finally picks up the courage to tell Veronica the truth. But he's also got a secret, he's already married! Veronica's mother, Carol, brings around five thousand pounds that Veronica's father left for a wedding. Kev and Veronica decided to use the money to pay for their house but fake a wedding.
Meanwhile Ian Gallagher is pursued by a female classmate. Little does she know he is actually gay. When he rejects her advances she sets her lethal brothers onto him.
The fake wedding doesn't go to plan when Veronica's crazy brother, Marty, escapes from jail. He locks himself into the bathroom and threatens to set Veron</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.5</Rating>
  <RatingCount>13</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Danny Brocklehurst|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/296352.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1387700180</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>15750</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>296353</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>4</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>|Mark Mylod|</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Episode 4</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>4</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2004-02-03</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>The Gallaghers have a big problem on their hands when a local child goes missing from a party.
Debbie steals/kidnaps a baby from the estate. However, the local residents immediatly think that the kid has been kidnapped by a pervert not least because Frank thinks he saw one outside the house of the missing girl.
The race is on to find the girl while the Gallaghers, Veronica &amp; Kev come up with a madcap scheme to get the baby back. It looks set for disaster but somehow they manage to get it off.
The baby is returned and Debbie is flooded with money and praise by the Police little knowing she actually kidnapped the kid in the first place.
Meanwhile after all the excitement Karen Jackson seduces Frank and they pair embark on a dangerous and likely disasterious affair.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.9</Rating>
  <RatingCount>10</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Paul Abbott|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/296353.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1387700194</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>15750</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>296354</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>5</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>|Mark Mylod|</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Episode 5</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>5</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2004-02-10</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Karen and Frank's affair continues behind the backs of Shelia and Lip. Shelia is concentrating on beating her phobea of open spaces, through a nurse that comes and visits her. Shelia goes shopping through a virtual reality machine but panics when she gets too near the doors.
Ian's affair with Kash is ruined after security cameras are installed in the shop to stop shop lifting. Yvonne notices strange behaviour and comes to the correct conclusion. She tells Kash that she wants another baby and decides that Ian can stay on at the shop but his relationship with Kash is over.
Lip discovers Karrens and frank's affair and goes crazy. He attacks his father.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>8.3</Rating>
  <RatingCount>7</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Carmel Morgan|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/296354.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1387700214</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>15750</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>296355</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>6</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>|Dearbhla Walsh|</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Episode 6</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>6</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2004-02-17</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Balifs are after Frank and the large amount of money he owns them. But Frank is too busy trying to fool his ex-wife out of hiding. He gets Shelia to ring up Monica and tell her that she has won a raffle, at the local supermarket. But Shelia is devestated when she tells Monica that Carol Vordaman is doing the prize giving and Monica doesn't know who Carol is!
At the supermarket Frank is spotted by Monica and her lesbian partner, Norma, and a halirious car chase begins (a spoof of Duel/Road Kill). Monica and Norma follow Frank and Kev back to Shelia's where Debbie spots her mother. Monica is hurt when Debbie ignores her and returns home.
Fiona and the other kids, apart from Lip and Debbie, turn up at Shelia's to see their mother. Upstairs Shelia tries it on with Norma.
A family meal between mother and children ends in disaster when Monica comes out as gay and Fiona walks out.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.9</Rating>
  <RatingCount>7</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Paul Abbott|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/296355.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1387700229</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>15750</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>296356</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>7</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>|Dearbhla Walsh|</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Episode 7</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>7</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2004-02-24</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>The balifs and Mr Wilson are still after Frank. And Frank seems to be more interested in spending time with his ex-wife, Monica, than dealing with his spiraling debts. However, much to Frank's annoyance Norma, Monica's lesbian partner, gives Frank a good idea, to fake his own death!
Meanwhile Maggie realises that Frank isn't as interested in her as she hoped. When Anthony comes around to talk about Fiona she accidentally gets Chilli in her eyes and staggers out into the Garden! The first time she has been out in five years!
Tony has finally found the perfect way to get rid of Steve and get with Fiona for he has stumbled across Steve's car stealing scam.
The balifs aren't so convinced that Frank is dead until one of them attacks Frank in his coffin, in front of the family! When Frank doesn't stir the balif finally realises that Frank is really dead, and how sick his violent outburst/attack seemed.
At Frank's wake Frank bursts out of the coffin and a party starts. Maggie turns up to ever</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>8.3</Rating>
  <RatingCount>7</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Paul Abbott|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/296356.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1387700244</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>15750</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>296358</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>1</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>|David Evans|</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Episode 1</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>1</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2005-01-04</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Frank is forced to take a job as a window cleaner when his father arrives. But is the window cleaning round really the best form of employment for Frank?
Meanwhile Karen eyes up Kev down the pub.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>5</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Paul Abbott|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/296358.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1387700275</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>15751</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>168</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>304</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>296359</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>2</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>|David Evans|</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Episode 2</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>2</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2005-01-11</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Frank takes a call while partying at Kev and Veronica's, but only much later does he pass on the message that social services are coming to discuss fostering. After a mad clean up, the social worker arrives with a child in tow. Next morning, the boy collapses at breakfast. After an anxious rush to hospital, it is found that he is suffering from nothing more life-threatening than the digestion of last night's leftover hash cake.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>6.8</Rating>
  <RatingCount>4</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Paul Abbott|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/296359.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1387700290</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>15751</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>168</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>304</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>296360</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>3</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>|Peter Lydon|</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Episode 3</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>3</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2005-01-18</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>A gardening competition is launched, by the council, to find the best garden and reward the winners with a years free rent! Naturally the shabby gardens of the Chattersworth estate suddenly turn into gardens fit for the queen. Carol doesn't wish to loose the winning prize and turns the Gallagher's garden from old wreck to sparkling garden. Veronica wants to do up their garden but Kev isn't too keen, that is until he meets with Tommy who works for the council. Together they steal a Diana Memorial Garden (!) and move it into their back yard.
Carol see's it as a declaration of war between mother and daughter and when the garden is trashed things turn even nastier between the warring family. It's later revealed that a group of yobs were responsible for trashing the garden, and others, but this does little to end the argument.
Meanwhile Shelia leaves to visit her sick mother in a hospice and leaves Frank with baby Nigel and Delia. The Jockey is raided and closed down for serving alcohol past closing hours.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.3</Rating>
  <RatingCount>4</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Danny Brocklehurst|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/296360.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1387700303</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>15751</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>312</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>296361</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>4</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>|Dearbhla Walsh|</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Episode 4</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>4</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2005-01-25</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Plans are afoot for Steve and Fiona's upcoming wedding. They pay a visit to the local vicar who eventually agrees to let them marry in the church but only after Steve agrees to pay a lot of money. Then disaster strikes when his car is stolen outside the church. Steve begins to panic and calls Tony. However, unknown to Steve Tony has actually stolen it for a joke but decides to look inside the car and finds a lot of money and drugs.
Veronica becomes convinces her mother is going crazy when she continues to talk to her dog. Marty packs her off on a mystery cruise and then takes the dog to have an operation to loose its voice!
Steve persaudes Tony to hand over the car. Steve drops the car off with some drug dealers but Tony and Stan turn up. Things turn nasty when a gun is pulled and then fired. One of the drug dealers is killed and the other one escapes but is quickly captured. A warrant is issued for Steve's arrest and he has to flee the estate.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>5.3</Rating>
  <RatingCount>3</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Paul Abbott|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/296361.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1387700316</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>15751</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>168</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>304</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>296362</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>5</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>|Dearbhla Walsh|</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Episode 5</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>5</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2005-02-01</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Sheila asks Lip to water the plants for a neighbour who's away on holiday, but the house is burgled and Lip is arrested by a bent copper, stitched up and charged. Frank goes to the police station and makes matters a lot worse. Debbie copies videos from Kash's shop and rents them around the estate, but one of her customers accidentally returns a home-made porn tape featuring the local lollipop lady</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.3</Rating>
  <RatingCount>6</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Phil Nodding|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/296362.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1387700330</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>15751</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>168</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>304</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>296363</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>6</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>|Dearbhla Walsh|</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Episode 6</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>6</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2005-02-08</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Lip is sleeping with Mandy while she pretends to be Ian's girlfriend to hide the fact that he's gay. However, after Mandy falls pregnant with Lip's baby everyone thinks Ian's the dad and the Maguires welcome him to the family - with the threat of castration if he doesn't marry her. Fiona gets mugged on her way home from a drunken night out.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.3</Rating>
  <RatingCount>7</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Danny Brocklehurst|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/296363.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1387700343</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>15751</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>296364</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>7</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>|David Evans|</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Episode 7</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>7</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2005-02-15</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Ladies Night at the Jockey proves to be more trouble than its worth. For one thing its full of blokes which only serves to anger Jez. Fiona eyes up footballer Ryan but when she wakes up the next morning it isn't Ryan who is lying next to her. Instead its the less-than-desirable Joey Dawson.
Fiona decides to take contraception but before she can actually take them Liam swallows them and then Marty traps Joey's arm in a door. At the hospital they discover that Joey's arm is broken but Liam is fine and there will be no ill effects.
A follow up visit from social services isn't as simple for the Gallagher family. The inspector is Katrina a woman who went to school with Fiona and who's life was appearantly hell because of Fiona dubbing her &quot;&quot;Sperm Whale&quot;&quot;. But the family pass the visit but Katrina reveals she's engaded-to Joey Dawson. At the Jockey Joey confesses he loves Fiona while Ryan lets slip to Katrina that Fiona and Joey were all over each other the night before.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.8</Rating>
  <RatingCount>5</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Amanda Coe|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/296364.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1387700356</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>15751</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>168</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>304</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>296365</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>8</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>|David Evans|</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Episode 8</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>8</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2005-02-22</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>After walking out of her job at the nursery, Fiona confesses to Veronica that she is pregnant by Craig and hasn't told him. Frank falls foul of two shifty accident claims salesmen after being hit in the mouth by Kash's shop door. Kash and Yvonne cannot afford to pay out and are forced to close the shop.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>6</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|John Griffin|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/296365.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1387700368</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>15751</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>312</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>296366</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>9</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>|Dearbhla Walsh|</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Episode 9</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>9</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2005-03-01</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Debbie's on a mission to help Marty who has an impending court appearance for a breach of the peace. Fiona is suffering from morning sickness, so Craig is planning a surprise trip to Wales to relax. Craig's wife, Sue, is jealous of his new relationship and seeks a showdown at the Gallaghers' house.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>6.8</Rating>
  <RatingCount>4</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Danny Brocklehurst|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/296366.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1387700383</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>15751</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>312</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>296367</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>10</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>|Dearbhla Walsh|</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Episode 10</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>10</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2005-03-08</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>The local elections are underway and Kash is running to be Chatsworth's councillor against dirty-dealing Bernie Creme. However, it turns out that Bernie is just a racist who exposes himself to the entire pub and loses all his supporters.
Lillian's husband is involved in a tragic accident which, at first, appears to be caused by Tony and Stan's Police van. But it later turns out that moments before he was hit by the van he was shot in the head. And it seems he was a junkie, according to the Police. Lillian is dashed off down the Police station to be interviewed about her late husband while Carol realises who shot him-Carl! Tony and Stan quickly figure out it was Carl as well due to CCTV footage. The family (bar Fiona who doesn't know) rallies behind Carl and just about manage to get him off the hook. Frank meanwhile decides to take the deadman's indentiy to get his benifits and then tries to kill his pet dog through various methods.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>8.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>4</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Paul Abbott|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/296367.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1387700406</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>15751</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>312</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>771301</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>1</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>3</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Catherine Morshead</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Episode 1</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>1</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2006-01-03</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>When five year-old Liam denounces religion at his RC Primary School and is subject to a home-visit by his teacher and the local priest, sister Debbie has to think fast. But shaving his head and pretending that he is dying of cancer is NOT one of Debbie's better ideas. In fact, by the time the rest of the Gallagher clan realise what's going on and try to set the record straight, the news has leaked out into the wider community and Debbie's lie lands the family in true Gallagher-style catastrophe. Could things get any worse for Debbie? </Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>6.8</Rating>
  <RatingCount>5</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>3</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Daniel Brockelhurst</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/771301.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1303456252</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>15752</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>312345</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>2</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>3</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Episode 2</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>2</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2006-01-10</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>Sally Carman|Christine Bottomley|Yasmin Bamford|Mike Woodhead|Amy Searles|Michael McNulty|Rory McCann</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Ian meets Jack and soon begins an affair with him. What will Kash say if he learns the truth, and more importantly, why is Jack behaving suspiciously?</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>3-1</ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.8</Rating>
  <RatingCount>6</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>3</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Paul Abbott</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/312345.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1303449742</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>15752</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>312346</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>3</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>3</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Episode 3</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>3</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2006-01-17</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>Katie Wimpenny|Martin Reeve|Steve Bell</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Mandy goes into labour after a run in with a masked robber inside the corner shop. Lip desperately wants to visit his new daughter, but will Mandy's parents allow the visit? And if not, just what will it take for Lip to prove himself to them...?</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>3-2</ProductionCode>
  <Rating>8.4</Rating>
  <RatingCount>5</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>3</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Paul Abbott</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/312346.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1303449796</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>15752</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>168</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>304</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>312347</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>4</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>3</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Episode 4</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>4</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2006-01-24</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>Katy Cavanagh|Sarah Parks|Andrew Sheridan|Denise Kennedy|Toby Hadoke|Graeme Hawley</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>When Carol discovers her best friend Lillian had an affair with her husband back in the seventies, she takes revenge by reporting her to the DSS for benefit fraud. Frank Gallagher, who has been posing as Lillian's dead husband and claiming his benefits, comes under suspicion.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>3-3</ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.8</Rating>
  <RatingCount>4</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>3</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Paul Abbott</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/312347.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1303449800</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>15752</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>320</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>312348</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>5</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>3</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Jonny Campbell</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Episode 5</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>5</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2006-01-31</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>Rob James-Collier|Maxton G. Beesley|Jill Halfpenny</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>On the day that Kev should be happily celebrating his 35th birthday, his mother throws herself from her balcony. To add to his woes, he sees his ex-wife Roxy, who's recently out of prison and far from reformed, at the funeral. Fatherhood has had a positive effect on Lip and Mandy.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>3-4</ProductionCode>
  <Rating>8.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>4</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>3</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Danny Brocklehurst</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/312348.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1303449804</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>15752</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>320</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>312349</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>6</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>3</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Episode 6</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>6</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2006-02-07</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>Nichola Burley|Clive Bonelle|Paula Wolfenden|John Peat|Marcus Hercules|Lindzey Cocker|James Wells</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>The Gallagher clan can't believe it when Carl starts to bring money into the household - but his mini-enterprise involves growing cannabis for the Maguires and the police are quick to bust him. Lip is jealous when Mandy gets a new boyfriend and he later discovers that she was the brains behind Carl's business.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>3-5</ProductionCode>
  <Rating>8.2</Rating>
  <RatingCount>5</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>3</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Paul Abbott</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/312349.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1303449809</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>15752</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>320</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>312350</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>7</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>3</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Paul Norton Walker</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Episode 7</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>7</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2006-02-14</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>Michael Hilton|Steve Hester|Tony Mooney|Sarah Kirkman|Ian Reddington|Justina Skillen|Matthew Gerrod</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Debbie has a new best friend who is everything she wants to be and has the boys falling at her feet. Suddenly Debbie realises what other girls her own age have been getting up to and what she's been missing out on while left holding the fort at home. Sue disappears leaving Marty to deal with the debt collectors in the only way he knows how.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>3-6</ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.5</Rating>
  <RatingCount>4</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>3</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Paul Abbott</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/312350.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1303449813</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>15752</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>312</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>312351</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>8</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>3</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Paul Norton Walker</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Episode 8</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>8</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2006-02-21</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>Trevor Williams|Jake McDonald|Margaret Henshaw|Maggie Fox</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>In preparation for her wedding to Frank, Sheila commissions the building of a conservatory in her back yard - but she suddenly remembers her first husband is buried under the patio. Veronica's last stab at IVF on the NHS fails, so she hatches a macabre plan to raise cash for private treatment.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>3-7</ProductionCode>
  <Rating>9.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>2</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>3</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Paul Abbott</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/312351.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1303449817</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>15752</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>312</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>319730</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>1</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>4</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>New Beginnings</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>1</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2007-01-09</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>The Gallaghers' return for a fourth series, and its Lip's 18th birthday but not all is going to be clean sailing as there’s a few surprises ready to hit him. First the Maguires expect him to do something for them. But the biggest shock of all is his long-lost mother Monica turning up out of the blue with a bombshell that could turn their lives upside down.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>8.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>4</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>4</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/319730.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1369610433</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>16641</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>319731</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>2</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>4</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>New Romances</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>2</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2007-01-16</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Frank’s desperate to keep the fact that he’s still married to estranged wife Monica from Sheila, and Monica’s not making it easy for him. But Sheila can see that she has competition for Frank and sets about trying to reunite Monica with her estranged lesbian lover. But is Monica still a lesbian?</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>8.3</Rating>
  <RatingCount>4</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>4</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/319731.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1369610459</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>16641</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>320</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>319732</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>3</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>4</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>You Decide</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>3</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2007-01-23</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Monica manages to seduce Frank and sink her claws back in, but he dare not tell Sheila that he and Monica have been sleeping together. Sheila proves to be a frightening adversary when scorned and Frank could be in real danger. But neither Sheila nor Monica want to share him and he has to decide on which wife he wants. But who will he choose?</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>8.7</Rating>
  <RatingCount>3</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>4</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/319732.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1369610484</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>16641</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>320</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>319733</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>4</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>4</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>The Runaway</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>4</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2007-01-30</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Ian gets more than he bargained for when a new person enters his life. Another death in the Maguire household causes Mimi to think the family may be cursed.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>9.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>2</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>4</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/319733.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1369610504</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>16641</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>319734</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>5</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>4</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Boys, Boys, Boys</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>5</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2007-02-06</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Debbie's glad to have her dad back at home, but Monica's not happy with all the attention Frank is giving her and tells her it's time she found herself a boyfriend. Also Ian catches the eye of someone he least expected.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>8.7</Rating>
  <RatingCount>3</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>4</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/319734.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1369610525</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>16641</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>319735</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>6</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>4</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Dangerous Situation</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>6</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2007-02-13</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Carl wants his family back together and that means getting rid of Norma - for good. Unfortunately, things don't go to plan when Norma proves to be a very tough adversary. Frank agrees to work on Shane's ice cream van - the Maguires use it as a cover for dealing and Frank's got E's on tap! However, there's trouble brewing.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.5</Rating>
  <RatingCount>4</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>4</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/319735.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1369610548</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>16641</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>320</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>319736</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>7</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>4</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Terrorist Target</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>7</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2007-02-20</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Explosions across the estate spark fears that Chatsworth is a terrorist target. But it has the Maguire's worried that they're under threat from folk a little closer to home when Patrick finds the family semtex missing. Meanwhile when Frank reveals to Monica she was never his first choice over Sheila, Monica vents her anger by turning to Norma for gifts and goodies.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>8.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>3</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>4</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/319736.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1369610575</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>16641</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>168</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>304</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>319737</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>8</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>4</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Revelations</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>8</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2007-02-27</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Learning of the death of his three ex-cell mates is sending Paddy round the bend. With the three of them taken out one-by-one in suspicious circumstances, could this mean he's next in line?</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>8.3</Rating>
  <RatingCount>3</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>4</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/319737.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1369610595</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>16641</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>320</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>347167</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>1</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>5</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>David Threlfall</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>The Countdown</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>1</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2008-01-01</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>Alice Grice|Alex Moxam|PJ Devlin|Mary Sobers|Darren Connelly|Karen Bryson|Roger Kennedy|Emily Bowker|Craig Shepherd</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>An emergency visit to the hospital results in Frank receiving devastating news, prompting him to embark on an orgy of drink and drug-fuelled mayhem, which culminates in a bizarre, drug-induced encounter with his younger self. Elsewhere, Lillian comes up with a surprising way to make money, and Lip's shady past catches up with him and leads to a no-holds-barred fight in The Jockey, with shocking consequences.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>9.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>3</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>5</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Ed McCardie</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/347167.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1369610640</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>29951</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>312</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>347168</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>2</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>5</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>David Threlfall</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Other Paddy</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>2</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2008-01-08</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>Jodi Hamblet|Sarah Byrne|Simon Lawson|Qasim Akhtar|Brian McCardie</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Mimi is forced to confront her deepest insecurity after an ex-boyfriend makes a cruel comment about her weight, and Paddy's inability to back up her up forces a wedge between the loving couple. And Carl takes offence when Ian becomes romantically involved with his teacher, ruining his chance at wooing a promiscuous fellow pupil.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.7</Rating>
  <RatingCount>3</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>5</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Stephen Russell</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/347168.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1369610661</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>29951</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>312</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>347169</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>3</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>5</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Happy Birthday, Ma Maguire</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>3</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2008-01-15</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>Sarah Byrne</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Monica seeks to make up for lost years with her children after failing a pregnancy test. Paddy is livid after the Jockey is robbed before Mimi's surprise birthday party, leaving Karen with the responsibility of arranging the bash from scratch. Stan becomes smitten when his pen-pan from the Ukraine pays a visit, but Carrie suspects that the charming foreigner has an ulterior motive.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.7</Rating>
  <RatingCount>3</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>5</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/347169.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1369610687</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>29951</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>312</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>347170</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>4</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>5</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Paul Norton Walker</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Frank's Big Win</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>4</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2008-01-22</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>Qasim Akhtar|Sarah Byrne|Gerard McLaughlin|Julian Walsh|Reece Hampton|Ralf Casson|Helena Fox|Wendy Patterson|Declan Wilson|Amir Farzaneh|Ian Braddock</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Frank Gallagher has won the lottery; or so the residents of Chatsworth think when Yvonne announces it on the local news. And Frank's not about to announce that he's never bought a lottery ticket in his life when free drinks are coming his way. But will he 'fess up when Liam is kidnapped and the ransom fee is his so-called winnings?</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.8</Rating>
  <RatingCount>4</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>5</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Jack Lothian</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/347170.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1369610704</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>29951</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>312</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>347171</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>5</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>5</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Beach Party</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>5</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2008-01-29</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Sarah Byrne|Qasim Akhtar|Sally Carman|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>With the local council doling out money to the new young-mayor, Debbie sees a chance to buy hens and potatoes and give Chatsworth free egg and chips. Meanwhile, Shane falls for his perfect woman and it looks like she's fallen for him but when she takes him back to her place, the spare room at Lillian's; Shane's in for a bit of a surprise. Also, Yvonne has trouble with some yobs in the shop and things get a bit heated has she finally met her natch? And,when Stan runs down an old lady, he confides to Tom and Carrie that he should be wearing spectacles. To save his job, Carrie takes the rap, but when the old lady decides to sue, it might be Carrie who is going to get fired.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.5</Rating>
  <RatingCount>4</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>5</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/347171.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1369610730</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>29951</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>312</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>347172</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>6</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>5</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Lawrence Till</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Nowhere to Go</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>6</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2008-02-05</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Sally Carman|Adam Beresford|Karl Lucas [I]|Lee Lomas|Colin David Jackson|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>A mishap with baby Katie and a bag of Es leads to a standoff between Mandy and Frank. When the family back Mandy, Frank is forced to leave the house and ends up sleeping rough.  Meanwhile, when Liam learns he's going to be nappy changing for Monica's new baby, he decides to run away. He catches up with Frank and the two outcasts bond over a camp fire and a leaky tent. Micky's attempts to get into his dad's good books go horribly wrong when he accidentally loses the weekly drug pick-up distracted by a hot guy from the local abattoir. He enlists Ian's help to get them back and the two lads go on an epic search until Ian gets caught by the thieves and Micky has to decide whether to save his friend or his own skin. Shane is delighted when Kellie finally admits that she loves him and he invites her round for Sunday lunch with the family. But Paddy is not happy about sitting round the table with a prostitute and decides to pay Kelly a little visit...</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.3</Rating>
  <RatingCount>3</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>5</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Ben Edwards</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/347172.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1392925527</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>29951</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>312</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>347173</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>7</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>5</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Fraser MacDonald</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Brothers and Boyfriends</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>7</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2008-02-12</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Matt Cross|Phil Corbitt|Alex Slater|Angela Holmes|Michelle Holmes|Martin Walsh|John Wilson|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>When there is a gas leak at the Gallaghers along comes a sexy fireman named Sean. He gets the attention of Ian and Mandy but which one of them will win the race to get the Sean into bed? Also, Carl finds himself in a risky situation.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.3</Rating>
  <RatingCount>4</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>5</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Stephen Russell</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/347173.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1369610784</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>29951</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>312</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>347174</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>8</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>5</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Fraser MacDonald</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>I Love Frank</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>8</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2008-02-19</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Esther Coles|Joanne King|George Whitton|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>On the bus to a re-start course, Frank has the briefest encounters with a beautiful stranger. Debbie invites some members of the church to stay, but has she got an ulterior motive. And Lillian's assigned to a witness protection programme.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>8.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>4</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>5</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Ed McCardie</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/347174.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1369610803</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>29951</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>312</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>352955</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>9</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>5</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Jim Loach</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Absent Parents</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>9</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2008-02-26</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>Anne Reid</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Monica has an unexpected visitor, her mother Joan, who no one's seen for twenty years. Suddenly all Monica's childhood insecurities come flooding back. But Joan has a secret, she's got Alzheimer's disease and has a very important task for Monica but, she can't remember what it is.  When Stan confesses to Yvonne that he's got a soft spot for her he gets a little more than he bargained for, in the stock room, up against the shelves and behind the frozen goods.  Yvonne is a woman with physical needs but does she want this to go any further because, Stan certainly does. When Paddy and Mimi take a holiday, Shane and Mickey decide to throw a party.  The only problem is, they've no cash to buy booze and drugs and when they enlist Liam to help them with a money making business venture, they soon find themselves outsmarted.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.5</Rating>
  <RatingCount>2</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>5</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Emma Frost</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/352955.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1369610843</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>29951</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>320</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>352956</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>10</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>5</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Jim Loach</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Old Friends, New Enemies</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>10</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2008-03-04</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Kenny Doughty|Mina Anwar|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Jamie's ex-cellmate Mark comes to stay, but Karen doesn't trust him and the battle lines are drawn. Karen's got a fight on her hands if she's to prevent Mark from leading Jamie back into a life of crime. When Carl gets poor grades in his GCSEs, he realises everybody thinks he's a failure. So he sets out to prove them wrong and, with a little bit of help from Paddy, finds his real talent in the boxing ring. Yvonne gets a shock when she hears that her daughter Meena has arranged her own marriage. Meanwhile, Norma finds herself on a date. But is she over Monica yet?</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>2</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>5</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Jack Lothian</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/352956.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1369610865</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>29951</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>320</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>352957</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>11</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>5</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Twin</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>11</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2008-03-11</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>When Paddy is caught on camera for an armed robbery and could face 20 years inside, Mimi begs him to call his brother, Noel. He's the only one who can help. But Paddy has a dark history with his sibling and would rather go to jail than ever set eyes on him again. As the reality of his situation dawns, he realises he has no choice. The Gallaghers find themselves three grand in debt to Mimi after Frank inhales a box of her drugs, and it seems that Ian is the only one who can bail the family out. But when his business venture fails, Ian finds he has nowhere to turn. In an act of desperation, he steals money from the till at the Jockey but things quickly spiral out of control. The status quo gets altered in the police house when Carrie becomes a sergeant. Tom is peeved that Carrie is exploiting her new position, but a chance comment leads him to discover a dark secret in Carrie's past, which means he can regain the upper hand...</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.5</Rating>
  <RatingCount>2</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>5</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/352957.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1369610883</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>29951</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>320</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>352958</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>12</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>5</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Lawrence Till</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Family at War</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>12</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2008-03-18</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Shahid Ahmed|Ben Owen-Jones|Sebastian Shaw|Kitty Simpson|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>When Stan gets caught in the crossfire between Yvonne and her kids, a full-blown row puts their relationship on the rocks.  Things go from bad to worse when Yvonne finds herself held at gunpoint in the shop.  Stan comes to the rescue but any hopes of this leading to an easy reconciliation are thwarted when the gun goes off and Stan lies bleeding amongst the cut-price yoghurts. Monica starts to panic when she discovers that the delivery date for her baby could be sooner than she thought. Faced with the unbearable last weeks of pregnancy and dreading maternal failure, she concludes that the only way through is to face her fears, bring on the birth and get it all over and done with. Carl announces that he's going to join the army. After all, there are some good perks: lots of travel, learn a trade and the girls love a guy in uniform.  But can he really put himself up as canon fodder?</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>8.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>2</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>5</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Malcolm Campbell</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/352958.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1392925556</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>29951</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>320</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>352959</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>13</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>5</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Date a Death</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>13</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2008-03-25</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Mandy looks set for an upturn in her love life when she's persuaded to go on a blind date by Karen, Jamie and Ian. It seems she's struck gold and is onto a keeper, until her first night of sex and drugs turns into a nightmare. Finding themselves with a corpse on their hands, Karen and Mandy have to work out how to get rid of the evidence before they're charged with murder. It's a long night for the girls as they drag a heavy wheelie bin around the estate...</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>8.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>2</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>5</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/352959.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1392925567</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>29951</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>320</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>352960</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>14</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>5</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>David Threlfall</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>The Ties That Blind Us</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>14</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2008-04-01</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Sacha Parkinson|Mark Hallet|Lesley Nicol|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>After Mandy gets arrested for suspected drug running she forms the most unlikely of friendships and finds herself helping Tom search for his real mother. The friendship, however, soon becomes something deeper for Mandy and with the help of Ian, she sets out to win Tom's heart. But do Tom's affections lie elsewhere? Mimi's short fuse gets the better of her when she harms her favourite son, Micky. Desperate to rein in her temper she attends anger management courses and gradually evolves as a new, sensitive woman - and responsible drug dealer. Seeing his business going down the pan, Patrick despairs and knows he has to get his old Mimi back or they'll go bankrupt. In an attempt to impress a new girlfriend, Carl enlists Karen as his personal sex counsellor, but is he getting help or getting off?</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.5</Rating>
  <RatingCount>2</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>5</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Ed McCardie</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/352960.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1369610954</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>29951</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>320</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>352961</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>15</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>5</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Assault</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>15</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2008-04-08</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>While enjoying another secret rendezvous, Debbie and Tom are forced to come to the aid of an assaulted woman, but things go horribly wrong when Tom gets arrested on suspicion of being the attacker. Only Debbie can supply his alibi, but not without putting both of them in a compromising position. There's a gruesome showdown between Shane and Paddy over Shane's girl, leaving Mimi torn between her love for her husband and the love she feels for her son. When Norma wakes up in a stranger's jogging bottoms after a night on the tiles, she sets off on a wild goose chase to find out whoever it was she slept with.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>8.5</Rating>
  <RatingCount>2</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>5</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/352961.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1369610976</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>29951</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>320</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>352962</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>16</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>5</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>The Ninth Time Around</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>16</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2008-04-15</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>When Manchester experiences an earth tremor, Monica's waters break and she goes into labour. On the other side of Chatsworth, the same tremor knocks Frank off of his barstool and puts him in a coma. Monica's refusing to have the baby unless Frank is present, but how long can she keep her bun in the oven?  While he's out cold in his hospital bed, Frank experiences an alternative world: a life where he is a success, where Ian isn't gay and Debbie looks like she'll never leave home. It's the world as Frank would have it; or is it? Carl is finding new success with girls by posing as a single parent. It's all going very well until his latest target runs off with the baby. Meanwhile, Shane has a proposal to put to Kelly.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>5-16</ProductionCode>
  <Rating>8.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>2</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>5</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/352962.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1369611002</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>29951</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>320</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>426080</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>1</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>6</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Remember Me</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>1</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2009-01-27</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Ian is attacked and left shaken and confused as to what he could have done to provoke it. When the stranger strikes again, Ian is left hospitalised and there's more bad news when he regains consciousness: he's got amnesia.

Suddenly he's an alien amongst his own family and friends, and even his own sexuality is a mystery.

Meanwhile it's Debbie's 16th birthday. Tom decides it's time to go public with their relationship, but Debbie has doubts about whether their relationship was ever really serious.

Kelly has bad news for Shane about her pregnancy; Frank and Monica are faced with an impossible challenge when they hear the voice of newborn baby Stella: but do they want to know what she has to say about her parents and Chatsworth?

And Ian's amnesia brings him a whole new perspective on his life, leaving him questioning if Chatsworth is the place for him after all.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>8.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>4</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>6</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/426080.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1369611059</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>39581</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>429536</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>2</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>6</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Trouble in Paradise</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>2</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2009-02-03</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>With the launch night of the newly redecorated Jockey looming, Jamie and Karen are feeling the pressure in their relationship. The honeymoon period is well and truly over - but can a lesbian encounter put the spice back into their marriage?
In the wake of Ian's departure, Micky looks to expand his horizons and enrols on a film course. Soon Micky discover a hidden talent and new friends; his tutor Liz and her husband Ady. The couple soon introduce him to the world of swinging when together they seduce him into their bed. 
An accident sends Carl to hospital where he takes up a job and is befriended by auxiliary nurse Maxine. Maxine is introduced to the rest of the Gallaghers, but Carl feels left out when Debbie and Maxine spark up a friendship.
Meanwhile Stan's attempts to bond with Chesney and Meena land them in trouble with the police and Norma makes a grim discovery while refurbishing the Jockey. And Mandy meets a new man in the form of Jamie's football team mate, Joe.
</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>8.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>3</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>6</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/429536.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1392925625</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>39581</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>431614</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>3</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>6</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>All Rise</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>3</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2009-02-10</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Frank is not happy when he finds out that he has been a victim of identity fraud. He finds that he is eligible for jury service after his criminal record is wiped clean. Shane and Micky scam some local tourists but Carrie is soon on their case.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.8</Rating>
  <RatingCount>4</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>6</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/431614.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1369611084</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>39581</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>434851</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>4</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>6</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Loving Wife</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>4</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2009-02-17</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Monica feels unwanted when Frank rejects her advances, and attends a hypnotist's show at the Jockey in the hope of regaining her sex appeal. Carl's new job leads to an intimate encounter, but after discovering he has an STI, he sets out to track down all his previous partners. Meanwhile, Paddy sets out to catch the people who desecrated Fergal's grave and Mickey's love life hits a stumbling block</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>6.5</Rating>
  <RatingCount>2</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>6</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/434851.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1369611113</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>39581</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>438111</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>5</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>6</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Paul Norton Walker</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Miscarriage of Marriage</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>5</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2009-02-24</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Karen's relationship with Jamie is put under strain when she suffers a miscarriage, unaware she was pregnant to begin with, and matters are made worse by the Maguires' extreme reaction. Liam wins a modelling competition that Debbie entered him in, Tom takes his prank war with Stan too far, and Carl gets into trouble with the female residents of the Chatsworth estate</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.7</Rating>
  <RatingCount>3</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>6</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Tom Higgins</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/438111.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1369611139</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>39581</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>438112</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>6</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>6</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Breaking Point</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>6</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2009-03-03</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Paddy wakes up to find himself chained to a bed in a strange room, unable to remember how he got there, and tension arises between Frank and Monica following a DSS investigation. Carl schemes to discover Micky's sexuality, Tom's last-ditch romantic gesture to regain Debbie's affection backfires, and Carrie decides it is time for a change</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>8.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>2</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>6</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/438112.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1369611152</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>39581</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>442224</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>7</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>6</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Always Leave Them Wanting More</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>7</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2009-03-10</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Ian drives a car back to the United Kingdom following his travels overseas unaware there is something hidden in it. With her wedding anniversary just around the corner and a party planned, Mimi becomes even more worried about Paddy's absence.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>2</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>6</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/442224.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1369611185</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>39581</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>312</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>444081</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>8</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>6</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Damaged</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>8</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2009-03-17</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Paddy returns and is determined to keep his heroin addiction a secret from the Maguires, while Mimi starts to think that he's got cancer. Meanwhile, when Frank inherits a house from an aunt, the Gallaghers celebrate a possible new start outside Chatsworth however, thing's aren't all as they first appear. After Kelly resigns from Lillian's brothel, she and Shane scam unsuspecting male clients in hotels across the city, until a sting goes horribly wrong leading to life threatning circumstances. Meanwhile, Jamie sabotages Karen's application for a wedding licence, and she reacts in a shocking way by standing strong ang making it clear that she'll never let the Maguires get hold of The Jockey.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>3</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>6</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/444081.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1369611231</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>39581</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>312</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>447881</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>9</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>6</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>The Darkest Hour</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>9</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2009-03-24</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Nobody is sure if Shane will ever be the same again after he is left partially paralysed by the accident, while Mimi and Kelly clash over who will help aid his recovery. After the departure of Monica, Norma contemplates her own future on the estate and a figure from the past offers her the chance of a fresh start. Elsewhere, Jamie settles back in with the Maguires and alarm bells ring for Karen when she suspects all is not right in Mandy and Joe's relationship</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>8.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>2</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>6</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/447881.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1369611229</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>39581</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>312</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>447891</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>10</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>6</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>To the Future</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>10</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2009-03-31</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Norma steps into Monica's shoes to help Liam's parents appear conventional in front of his head teacher, but Frank looks set to spoil his son's place on a scholarship. Meanwhile, Paddy is increasingly agitated by Mimi's efforts to wean him off drugs, and Karen sacks Jamie - only for Joe to propose taking his place. Lillian gets a surprise visit from her son Rodney, and Kelly recruits Meena to do Shane's physiotherapy</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>8.5</Rating>
  <RatingCount>2</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>6</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/447891.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1392925650</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>39581</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>312</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>507341</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>11</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>6</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Powerless</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>11</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2009-04-07</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Jamie beats Joe up after he discovers that he has been hitting Mandy. Mimi decides to take the blame for the attack to save her son from being sent back to prison. Paddy's secret comes out.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>6</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/507341.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1369611284</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>39581</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>320</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>514641</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>12</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>6</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Cold Turkey</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>12</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2009-04-14</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Ian becomes angry with Liam when he discovers that he has been skipping school. He soon finds out that Danny is responsible for Liam's absence and suspects that there is more to this than meets the eye.

Patrick goes cold turkey and faces his demons, but can he come out clean and make a fresh start? And although Mimi faces an uncertain prison sentence, her main concern is Patrick's past infidelity.

With Joe recovering, Mandy is under mounting pressure from all sides to leave him, but the decision is hers alone. And Meena takes her modelling career in a raunchy direction, much to Yvonne's disapproval.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>6</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/514641.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1369611303</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>39581</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>556601</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>13</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>6</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>What About Me?</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>13</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2009-04-21</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>The Gallagher unit is rocked when an unexpected visit from the social services catches them off guard and the family fall apart. In the aftermath Debbie unleashes her fury on Frank, which propels him on an almighty bender, but can Frank realise the solution to their problems won't be found at the bottom of a pint glass, before it's too late? Every teenage boy's fantasy becomes reality for Chesney when he is introduced to a married housewife who pops his cherry and he quickly falls head over heels.
</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>6</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/556601.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1369611335</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>39581</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>312</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>582081</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>14</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>6</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Haunted by the Past</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>14</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2009-04-28</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Yvonne's past catches up with her and she tries to stop Chesney and Meena from learning the truth.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>8.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>2</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>6</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/582081.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1369611361</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>39581</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>320</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>582091</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>15</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>6</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Confession</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>15</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2009-05-05</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>After Debbie throws him out for the night, Frank ends up in a confessional booth where he hears a neighbour's shocking confession. Frank finds himself drawn into what is going on.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.5</Rating>
  <RatingCount>4</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>6</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/582091.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1369611392</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>39581</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>312</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>582101</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>16</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>6</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>It's Over</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>16</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2009-05-12</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Patrick continues to loose his grip on his marriage and his family.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>8.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>2</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>6</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/582101.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1369611390</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>39581</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>176</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>312</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>1619921</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>1</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>7</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>David Threlfall</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Perfectly Frank</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>1</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2010-01-26</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>It's Frank's 50th and Liam has the dubious honour of sharing the auspicious day with him on his 11th birthday. Uncharacteristically, Frank snubs the chance of a party, and instead opts to dwell in his own lonely loveless existence until... Libby, a local librarian falls into his life.

His passion reignited, a whirlwind romance ensues - but will Libby's mother Patty (a full-time wheelchair user), bibliophile activists and riot police stand in the way of Frank holding onto his new love?

Meanwhile, Liam's inherited the dirty nappies, rubber gloves and responsibility of the Gallagher household. Nin, Liam's great grandmother, offers to move in and help ease his burden, but a selfish Frank rejects her. Liam is infuriated. Unable to cope herself, Nin is spurred into homicidal action and in turn teaches Liam a priceless lesson in surviving as a Gallagher.

Elsewhere, whilst an overdue Karen worries about the paternity of her unborn baby, an oblivious Jamie and the rest of the Maguire clan prepare for the imminent arrival. Joe lurks in the background, but a medical emergency soon brings him to the fore and back in favour with the Maguires.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.2</Rating>
  <RatingCount>5</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>7</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Tom Higgins</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/1619921.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1358709905</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>181491</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>1619941</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>2</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>7</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>David Threlfall</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Gunshot</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>2</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2010-01-26</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>The Maguire clan is fully mobilised for the christening of its newest member baby Connor, with Mimi pulling all the strings. Her first act, reallocating godmother duties, leaves now 'ex' godmother Kelly devastated.

Shane is stuck in the unenviable position of being forced to take sides between Kelly's need for acceptance and his mum's pursuit of respectability. Kelly demands he permanently cut the apron strings if their relationship is to last.

Paddy's attempt to get involved in the family celebration is derailed by his own personal credit crunch. Papering over the cracks in his relationships, Paddy tries to press-gang Shane and Jamie into his new plan for the family business. While the lads turn him down, an eager Mickey is overlooked.

Feeling ever more isolated, a fatal mistake by Paddy means Mickey must come to his rescue. At his lowest ebb, Paddy takes the christening opportunity to cleanse his own soul in front of the astonished family.

Meanwhile Karen's spending is burdening her and Jamie under a mountain of debt whilst her affair with Joe threatens to spiral out of control. At the Gallaghers, Carl's experiment in the bedroom shocks Maxine into retaliatory strap-on action!</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.8</Rating>
  <RatingCount>5</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>7</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Emma Taylor</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/1619941.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1358709895</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>181491</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>1619951</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>3</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>7</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Lawrence Till</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Out of Control</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>3</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2010-02-02</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Karen's obsessive drive to prove herself more than just a mum has Jamie worried. With the help of a trampoline and a battalion of baton twirling majorettes her body is in perfect shape but her mind is in danger of unravelling, leaving the Maguires to pick up the pieces.

Liam's pursuit of his first true love is threatened when he becomes tangled in a web of his own lies. His desperate attempts to conceal his Chatsworth life are shattered when Frank is summoned to the school.

Maxine's life is thrown into turmoil when she is presented with an urgent choice. At the time she needs Carl most she finds him following in Frank's footsteps at the bottom of a pint glass. She turns to Ian for support.

Elsewhere on Chatsworth, Yvonne is in debt and out of her depth when Paddy comes collecting. The Karibs concoct a plan leaving the shop under new management, Paddy enraged and Chesney starting a new independent life. Meanwhile, Mickey finds a plumber to help him with his neglected pipework.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.4</Rating>
  <RatingCount>5</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>7</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Sarah Hooper</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/1619951.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1358709885</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>181491</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>1695531</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>4</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>7</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Toyboy</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>4</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2010-02-09</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Mimi gets a toy boy, Billy the Jockey football team's star striker, but her happiness is short-lived when she discovers her new beau is the not the man she thought he was. So when Billy tries to blackmail Mimi into continuing to see him, she decides to teach him a Maguire life lesson he will never forget.

Shane and Kelly encourage Paddy to get back into the dating game; only to have their proposal rejected. Unperturbed, Shane rallies his brothers together and arranges a night out for Paddy. At the club Paddy's embarrassing 'Saturday Night Fever' dance routine cause his sons to abandon him. Emasculated, he returns home where he finds his own opportunity to make a proposal.

Elsewhere, Frank is temporarily blinded by bootleg vodka. Rejecting doctor's orders to detox, the family take advantage of his blindness and set about turning his vices into virtues. Joe settles in as the new manager of the shop and in an attempt to make more money on the side, makes a deal with Shane.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.6</Rating>
  <RatingCount>5</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>7</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/1695531.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1358709872</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>181491</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>1734391</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>5</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>7</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Paul Norton Walker</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>The Things You Do For Love</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>5</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2010-02-16</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Maxine is desperate to make a good impression at her parents' party so cajoles Ian into pretending to be her boyfriend. He reluctantly agrees, but their act unearths deep feelings that take everyone by surprise.

Meanwhile, Carl realises what he's lost by splitting up with Maxine so he is determined to win her back. But Carl soon finds love and hate are two sides of the same coin when Micky reveals a painful secret.

At the Jockey, Mimi does her best to conceal Karen's illness after she returns from the psychiatric unit. While Karen settles back into Chatsworth life, Jamie struggles to cope with the reality of living with mental illness. Escaping for a night out, Jamie meets Michelle, a Madame of a thriving male Escort Agency who plans to seduce him into a murky but lucrative new job.

While Lillian is away, Kelly takes control of the brothel and is soon making a fortune from an untapped market. Paddy is keen to get in on the action but Kelly's not interested, so he forces Chesney to become part of the Maguire organisation and accept an offer he can't refuse.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.5</Rating>
  <RatingCount>4</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>7</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Jack Lothian</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/1734391.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1358709862</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>181491</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>1771731</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>6</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>7</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>From Chatsworth to Cuba</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>6</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2010-02-23</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Paddy's plans to salsa into the sunset with his new love D'een are scuppered when Mimi forces him to guarantee the financial security of the family with one last job - targeting the drug money of notorious psychopath Roscoe. Torn between a new life with D'reen and his family responsibilities, Patrick calls upon his sons for help.

Meanwhile, Liam is suffocating under an avalanche of household debts and the fallout from trying to gamble his way out of trouble. Looked upon as a massive disappointment by Frank, and with no options left, he is driven to desperate measures.

And Jamie is literally flat-out trying to keep his family afloat while Karen is coming apart at the seams.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>5</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>7</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/1771731.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1392925680</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>181491</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>1812561</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>7</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>7</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Reunited</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>7</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2010-03-02</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Frank's romantic interest, Libby, returns and her time away has only increased her ardour. Armed with just a mobile library she is determined to bring knowledge to the people and rekindle her romance.

Libby's romantic delusion is only punctured when she witnesses the 'real' Frank, leaving her Elizabeth Bennett without the Mr Darcy she craved. But overwhelmed by his desire, Frank strains every sinew to win her back using an unfamiliar weapon, honesty.

Jamie focuses all his energies into giving his Madam, Michelle, whatever she wants in order to pay off Karen's debts.

But his unusual behaviour rattles Karen's delicate disposition and raises Paddy's suspicions and when Michelle makes it clear she wants more than Jamie can give, the pressure mounts.

Risking the fury of a woman scorned, but with everything he cares for at stake, Jamie has no choice but to find a way out.

Meanwhile, Lillian invests in a new HD television to keep the punters happy, but soon realises she has purchased a conduit to the afterlife.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>8.2</Rating>
  <RatingCount>5</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>7</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/1812561.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1358709833</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>181491</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>1817591</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>8</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>7</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Marry Me (1)</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>8</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2010-03-09</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Wedding bells are in the air on the estate, a little too frequently for the police, as the Maguire's exploit a new money-making scheme.

Business turns to pleasure when Shane asks Kelly to marry him, but his dream soon becomes a nightmare when she turns him down.

As his life unravels Shane uncovers a terrible betrayal by those closest to him and must suffer for the sins of his father. Hitting rock bottom he finds the strength to make an important decision.

Now Libby and her mother are firmly nestled in the Gallagher house, Frank 'volunteers' to paint Patty's converted bedroom.

But in the pursuit of a bargain, Frank falls and feigns injury leading to a potentially disastrous face-off with Patty.

Elsewhere, Chesney holds a house party to get close to Sammy, but a promise turns to a threat when blood is spilt, leaving awful consequences.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.3</Rating>
  <RatingCount>4</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>7</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/1817591.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1393867117</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>181491</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>1817601</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>9</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>7</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>The Wild Wales (2)</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>9</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2010-03-16</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Carl and Chesney's attempt to outrun their troubles make them realise the grass isn't always greener.

Stranded on a Welsh farm they are offered sanctuary by a mysterious woman, Hazel. But things soon turn sour when news reaches them that they are now the prime suspects for Bonehead's murder.

Back home, Liam and Maxine seem to be the only ones concerned by their disappearance which forces Ian to confront Jimmy, the real murderer, in order to establish the truth.

Elsewhere, Mickey and Liam have been picked by the council to make a local community film in the hope it will inspire the residents of Chatsworth now that their estate has been identified as the most run down in Britain.

With Kelly and Shane's help Mickey decides to stretch poetic licence in pursuit of glory, whilst Liam uses the competition as a cover to film evidence that could save Carl and Chesney from prison.

Meanwhile, in a bid to better herself, Mimi joins the WI, but is humiliated and ostracised by the group, who make it clear she will never belong. In revenge, Mimi decides to pep up their annual calendar shoot with her own special mixture.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.8</Rating>
  <RatingCount>4</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>7</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/1817601.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1393867133</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>181491</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>1817611</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>10</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>7</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Great Dangers (3)</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>10</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2010-03-23</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Shane is devastated to discover he's 'firing blanks' and while he frets, Kelly is reconciled to their future without children. The Maguire men refuse to let one of their own be struck down so decide to take matters into their own hands and get their heads together to come up with a sticky solution. Although Shane is keen to take up their offer Kelly refuses, and with Liam's help, both realise the answer to their problem lies closer to home.

Carl and Chesney return to the Chatsworth and live undercover in Joe's storeroom. When Maxine discovers the boys are back, she risks her relationship with Ian by secretly concocting a plan to get them out of trouble. Carl prefers a more direct option, which puts all the Gallaghers in danger. While others choose to turn a blind eye, including Paddy, Shane refuses to stand by and do nothing, teaching Jimmy and his gang a lesson they will never forget. Meanwhile, Libby's attempts to set up a book club backfire when she, with Frank's encouragement, becomes an unwitting modern-day Robin Hood.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>8.3</Rating>
  <RatingCount>3</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>7</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/1817611.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1393867143</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>181491</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>1976431</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>11</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>7</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Fallen Heroes</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>11</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2010-03-30</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Liam befriends World War Two veteran, Reggie, to help him with a school project. Troubled and lonely without his sister and fed up with Libby's well-intentioned interference at home, Liam finds solace in his friendship with the old man. But when Libby spies on them, she jumps to the all the wrong conclusions - leading to a tragic confrontation between the Gallaghers and Reggie.

Maxine is shocked when her brother, Bruce, turns up with a black eye claiming a homophobic attack by their dad, but her loyalties are tested when she confronts their father and discovers the real story. Bruce's arrival as an openly gay man on Chatsworth agitates the locals and he quickly outstays his welcome at Ian's house, but he charms his way into Mimi's heart and the Jockey, leaving Mickey teetering on the brink of a nervous breakdown.

Meanwhile, Karen is put out when Joe appears to have moved on by taking control of his life and attending anger management classes.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.3</Rating>
  <RatingCount>3</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>7</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/1976431.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1358709997</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>181491</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>1976441</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>12</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>7</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Boxer</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>12</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2010-04-06</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>In an attempt to build up some confidence, Ian joins the local boxing club and quickly strikes up a friendship with the owner, Jock. But when the club faces closure due to Jock's debt with Paddy, Ian enlists Maxine, Carl and Chesney to help raise funds. However, it soon becomes clear that Ian has stumbled into a hornet's nest of unfinished business between Paddy and Jock.

Meanwhile, a moment of heroism prompts Mickey to apply for a job with the fire service, but during the assessment he is haunted by old doubts. Returning a failure, he feels wounded, but his handling of a life-threatening emergency proves that he deserves respect.

At the Gallaghers', Libby's biological clock is in overdrive, and to Frank's utter horror she makes it clear she wants to have children of her own before it's too late.

Elsewhere, Liam is targeted by bullies, while Karen sets up a Chatsworth's Got Talent night at The Jockey.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.2</Rating>
  <RatingCount>5</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>7</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/1976441.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1358710007</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>181491</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>1976451</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>13</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>7</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Keep it in the Family</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>13</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2010-04-13</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Kelly takes guardianship of her 15 year-old half sister Tonya who is homeless and needs help to get her baby boy out of care. In a meeting with Tonya's social worker Julie, it's agreed that custody will only be considered if Tonya proves she is responsible by looking after a simulation baby. But it's not long before the unruly teen leaves Micky holding the plastic baby, forcing him to make a painful decision.

Elsewhere, Libby witnesses the results of an apparent miracle from a visit to a French grotto and organises a pilgrimage for Patty. Petrified and elated at the thought of liberation from her mother, she persuades Frank to escort Patty while she waits anxiously at home. The unlikely travelling companions end up sharing a room in a convent where Frank becomes the improbable focus of attention.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.3</Rating>
  <RatingCount>3</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>7</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/1976451.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1392925767</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>181491</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>2041561</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>14</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>7</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Secret Relations</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>14</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2010-04-20</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>After months of separation Patrick and Mimi amicably agree to a quickie divorce, but they get a nasty shock when it's revealed their marriage was never legal. Mimi flies into accusations and recriminations holding Patrick to blame. She then hatches a plan to secretly marry and divorce legitimately in order to save the souls of their children who were born out of wedlock.

Everything is in disarray, and Patrick is due to leave for a new business venture, but the mission to re-marry brings up memories of the past and unearths their true feelings. With his parents apparently divorced, Micky feels orphaned and bitter about his relationships. In an effort to cheer him up, Maxine and Ian treat him to a night out where he meets a guy, Gary. Their connection restores his faith until he discovers their bond is built on secrets and half-truths. Micky must decide whether to bare the burden of his own lies or if honesty is the best policy. Patty sets Frank up on a benefit scam, landing him behind bars. But when Libby learns the truth, she rails against a righteous Patty in order to raise bail and free her love.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>6.7</Rating>
  <RatingCount>3</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>7</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/2041561.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1358710035</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>181491</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>2150101</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>15</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>7</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>The End of the Affair</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>15</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2010-04-27</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>During his birthday celebration Joe receives the tragic news of his father's death. The painful realisation that life is too short fuels his determination to start a new life with Karen. Although Karen is uncertain, Joe manages to convinces her of their future together away from Chatsworth. Trying to come clean to Jamie, Karen's confession is derailed when he reveals his own grubby secrets. Emotional deadlock forces Joe into a course of action with far-reaching consequences for all of them. Elsewhere, Bruce gets a chance to shine as caretaker/manager for the Jockey football team, but when he arranges a gay five-a-side football tournament Chesney is not willing to 'come out' with the other lads. And while Ian plays with the boys, Maxine explores her artistic side as a life model.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.3</Rating>
  <RatingCount>3</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>7</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/2150101.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1392925783</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>181491</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>2153881</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>16</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>7</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Gang Wars</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>16</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2010-05-04</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Karen and Joe are holed up in the shop with the spectre of Jamie's revenge hanging over them. Joe is plotting their future away from Chatsworth, but Jamie has Connor in hiding and Karen isn't going anywhere without her son. Joe uses his dubious contacts to snatch Connor and drag his new family away to freedom, but little does he know he's carrying unwelcome baggage!

When Maxine and Ian are mugged they viciously fight back, taking their attacker captive. At odds on what to do with their prisoner, the couple quickly realise their relationship is falling apart. Elsewhere, a dark cloud falls over the Maguire family when notorious gangster and psychopath Roscoe shows up. The brothers scatter for cover, leaving Mimi to suffer the intimidation along with a dose of extreme indigestion.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>8.3</Rating>
  <RatingCount>4</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>7</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/2153881.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1358710061</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>181491</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>3417991</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>1</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>8</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Dominic LeClerc</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>The Night Before</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>1</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2011-01-10</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Libby and Frank are supposed to be getting married, but this is put on hold when Frank disappears on his stag night. Mimi tries to find out the identity of the father of her new baby Cilla. </Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.5</Rating>
  <RatingCount>4</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>8</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Tom Higgins</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/3417991.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384296477</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>388391</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>3418001</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>2</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>8</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Dominic LeClerc</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Missing</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>2</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2011-01-11</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Frank is still missing and imagines that he is in a parallel universe featuring Doctor Who characters. His ex-wife Monica, having heard that Frank has gone, wants custody of Stella and Liam. </Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>8.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>3</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>8</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Ian Kershaw</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/3418001.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384296517</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>388391</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>3418011</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>3</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>8</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Lawrence Till</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Where's Frank?</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>3</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2011-01-12</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Shane finds security work at the local school and helps a boy being bullied by his twin. Frank is still incarcerated in a psychiatric hospital, unknown to Libby, who tries to move on with her life. </Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>6.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>8</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Kevin Erlise</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/3418011.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384296535</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>388391</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>3418021</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>4</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>8</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Metin Huseyin</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Back Home</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>4</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2011-01-13</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>After returning to the Jockey, Karen attends the psychiatric hospital as an out-patient and finds that Frank has been there all along. Can he break free and save his relationship with Libby? Meanwhile, Sita is devastated when she fails her exams, and discovers her tutor will pass her if she sleeps with him. Determined to pass her exam, Sita turns to Carl for help. Elsewhere, Aiden, Patty's great nephew, arrives on Chatsworth following his mother's imprisonment, and he proves more than a match for various Chatsworth residents.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.8</Rating>
  <RatingCount>4</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>8</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Ed McCardie</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/3418021.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384296553</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>388391</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>3472271</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>5</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>8</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Lawrence Till</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Wedding of Disaster</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>5</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2011-01-14</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>After weeks of suffering at the hands of his own mental incarceration Frank is almost fully intact of his marbles and is plots his escape.

Libby meanwhile has had the dramatic news that Frank's divorce is about to be nullified and they could lose the family home in 24 hours. The solution is for Frank and Libby to get married and the clock is ticking...</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>6.8</Rating>
  <RatingCount>4</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>8</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Ed McCardie</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/3472271.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384296575</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>388391</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>3472281</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>6</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>8</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Metin Huseyin</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Gangster Gallagher</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>6</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2011-01-18</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>It's Carl's 21st birthday, and Frank, Libby and the Maguires are planning a suprise party for him. Carl gets a job working for Jamie. However, his first job does not go to plan when Kelly steals money which was supposed to go to a business client. The business client in question is a ruthless psychopath. Left alone with him, Carl faces the most darkest experience of his life, and his problems have only just begun when Jamie accuses him of trying to steal from the family. Meanwhile, one of Joe's money-making schemes comes back to haunt Chesney, leaving him and Sita in debt. Mickey encourages Chesney to set up a gay hotline. Chesney is reluctant, but Mickey is left wondering what he has started when Chesney becomes addicted to the hotline. </Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.8</Rating>
  <RatingCount>4</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>8</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Darren Fairhurst</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/3472281.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384296593</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>388391</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>3472291</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>7</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>8</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Paul Norton Walker</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Kidnap and Ransom</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>7</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2011-01-25</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID>tt1822007</IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Shane and Kelly's new business of giving people their sexual fantasy threatens the Maguire family business when their client, Sandra, is reported missing by her husband. As the police swarm Chatsworth searching for her &quot;Kidnappers&quot;, Shane calls upon the residents to help him, but Jamie is determined to make Shane see that he is not fit to run the business, even if it means sending his brother to prison. Meanwhile, Sita is annoyed to discover Chesney's new Muslim driving school scheme is a ruse for wild parties at the shop, and fearful that Chesney is losing everything the Karibs have worked for, Sita calls the terrorist line, but her actions result in a robbery at the shop, leaving the Karibs penniless. And, Patty, Mimi and Lillian go to battle over a bingo win, whilst Jackson becomes an unlikely drinking buddy for Frank. </Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.8</Rating>
  <RatingCount>4</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>8</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Jimmy Dowdall</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/3472291.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384296609</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>388391</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>3472301</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>8</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>8</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Paul Norton Walker</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Together in Heaven</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>8</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2011-02-01</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID>tt1826437</IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Mickey and Shane think of a way to make some extra money. Their final idea was to make a child pornography site which contained no nude images and took the credit card details of those who subscribed. Their view on the matter was that they were doing a good thing by using the website as a deterant, however the police didn't see it that way.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>3</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>8</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Phil Charles</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/3472301.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1392925801</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>388391</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>3604751</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>9</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>8</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Andy McDonnell</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Maguire Meltdown</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>9</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2011-02-08</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID>tt1832148</IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>After sleepless nights with Cilla, Mimi is starting to feel bad and believes that she is going mad, as one of her relatives did, and that the house is haunted. Finally she believes that Kelly and Shane are trying to kill her and locks them out of the house though she recovers after seeing a vision of Mandy, who tells her what to do. Kelly is suspicious of the power new girl Bonnie exerts over Lillian in the brothel, and Avril and Jackson's continuing efforts to spice up their sex life leads daughter Letitia to believe that her father is having an affair. </Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>6.3</Rating>
  <RatingCount>3</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>8</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Frank Rickarby</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/3604751.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384296644</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>388391</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>3604761</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>10</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>8</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Lawrence Till</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Sickness and Health</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>10</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2011-02-15</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID>tt1837356</IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Mickey needs somebody to love, He adopts a cat with FIDS (feline AIDS) and meets Philip who also suffers with AIDS in order to learn more about it. Mickey goes to the shop and returns to find Philip dead.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>8.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>3</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>8</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Tom Higgins</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/3604761.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384296658</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>388391</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>3710681</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>11</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>8</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Lawrence Till</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Takeover</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>11</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2011-02-22</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID>tt1842944</IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Libby gets her mother a nurse to look after her when she's at work, all doesn't go to plan when Libby's mother mis-treated. Lillian reveals that she has signed over the house to her newly adopted daughter, Bonnie. Bonnie tells Lillian about her life growing up and then commits suicide.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>3</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>8</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Ian Kershaw</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/3710681.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384296722</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>388391</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>3710691</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>12</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>8</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Paul Norton Walker</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Sibling Rivalry</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>12</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2011-03-01</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID>tt1848481</IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Mimi's transsexual sister turns up, but isn't all she appears to be. The Maguires are still at each others throats, and Chesney is in danger as he and Jackson join the British Alliance Party, and manage to rub them up the wrong way. </Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>3</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>8</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Darren Fairhurst</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/3710691.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384296699</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>388391</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>3809021</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>13</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>8</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Paul Norton Walker</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Beginnings and Ends</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>13</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2011-03-08</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID>tt1853782</IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Following his sexual encounter with Letitia's headmistress, Miss Heller, Frank has had his final chance with Libby, who seems taken with the mysterious Martin. Shane's theft of Tilly Pucker's wheelchair further strains relations between the Maguire brothers, coming to a head in a showdown with Tilly's minders. </Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.6</Rating>
  <RatingCount>5</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>8</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Kevin Erlis</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/3809021.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384296738</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>388391</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>3809031</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>14</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>8</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>The Not-So Deceased</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>14</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2011-08-30</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID>tt2041179</IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>It's a black day on Chatsworth when Paddy Maguire is returned in a coffin. While the residents grieve, Jamie gathers the Maguires to lift the lid on this 'special delivery'. Leticia dares Aiden to break in and take a photo of Paddy, but they're in for quite a surprise. Meanwhile, Karen sets up a kids' entertainment business, but the joke's on her when Mickey, Avril and Lillian join the team. Competition is fierce, but when a catfight with a sexy rival is popular with the dads, Karen discovers a new way to make some extra cash behind Jamie's back. Little does she know the danger she will face. Frank's war with Patty is re-ignited after Libby's departure, and he makes a shocking discovery that leaves Patty at his mercy. And Mimi gets a new strap-on!. </Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.5</Rating>
  <RatingCount>2</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>8</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/3809031.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384296753</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>388391</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>3809041</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>15</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>8</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Michael Keillor</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>My Name is Avril</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>15</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2011-09-06</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID>tt2056239</IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Avril is busy keeping secrets from her family; with no job and no money, but always a gift to hand, something doesn't quite add up. Mimi has designs on fit jogger Neil, but he's unsure of her advances - because he only wants sex. Mimi is keen to spice up her sex life, but Karen raises concerns about Neil's calorific role-play. When 12-year-old Bean tries to shoplift, Chesney phones her dad, Gorky, who is Chesney's delivery driver, but Chesney soon becomes concerned for Bean's welfare and decides to try and rescue her. And the law finally catches up with Avril when a bailiff arrives; she breaks down and confesses leaving Jackson gobsmacked. Will he and Letitia promise to support her and help pay back all the money she owes?</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>8</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Ian Kershaw</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/3809041.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1392925823</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>388391</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>3809051</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>16</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>8</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Sarah Punshon</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Frank Gallagher: Sent by God</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>16</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2011-09-13</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID>tt2056240</IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>While cleaning the windows, Jackson spots Letitia kissing Dee Davies in her bedroom. Jackson goes berserk, attacking Dee in front of a social worker who's waiting to assess him and Avril as foster parents. Frank isn't much use in the parent department, staggering to the Jockey and leaving Carl to nurse pox-ridden Stella. Drunken Frank then leaves the pub and accidentally gets on a mini-bus, waking up in a synagogue. He's discovered by Isaac, who promises not to report him because Frank's been sent from God. Frank thanks Isaac for his advice and hospitality by stealing his candelabra and legging it. Karen's fed up with how she's treated in her own pub and plots to get her power back with a card game. Meanwhile, an ambulance is called for the smallest Gallagher. Will she pull through unharmed?</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>8</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Tom Higgins; Lee Warburton</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/3809051.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1392925841</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>388391</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>3809061</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>17</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>8</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Paul Unwin</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Comebacks</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>17</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2011-09-20</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID>tt2056241</IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>A new gang has rolled into Chatsworth with an unlikely mission - to save the souls of the community. Jesus O'Toole leads the group and seems to know too much about certain residents. Aidan is certainly open to the possibilities that religion might bring, but love soon turns to hate when local businesses are picketed. An explosion on the Maguire's turf sees the family prepare for revenge. Kelly is attacked by a familiar face - Marty Fisher, who is on the run. And, Patty returns, missing Libby, she turns to the only person who might know of her whereabouts - Frank.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>8</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Tom Higgins</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/3809061.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384296799</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>388391</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>3809071</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>18</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>8</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Gordon Anderson</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Frank in the Frame</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>18</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2011-09-27</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>There's uproar in The Jockey when Frank pockets Cynthia's scratch card. And when Cynthia is assaulted, Frank becomes the prime suspect. Carl kicks off against the accusers, but Kelly shows Carl CCTV footage of Frank near the crime scene. Frank remembers nothing but scratch marks on his chest tell a different story. While Frank hands himself in, a distressed Carl seeks to prove his dad's innocence and phones Kev Ball, who returns to the Chatsworth like a knight in shining armour. New video footage jogs Frank's memory, but puts him in a stickier situation. Can a deal be made with gangster Growbag Macready? Frank's fate rests in his hands. Meanwhile, Mickey moves into the Jockey after a disagreement with Mimi, and Marty's presence continues to cause trouble between Shane and Kelly.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>9.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>8</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Paul Abbott</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/3809071.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1392925861</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>388391</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>3809081</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>19</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>8</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Paul Unwin</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Moving Back</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>19</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2011-10-04</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Aidan's bad behaviour has landed him in court, but it's Patty who'll decide the outcome. Feeling unwelcome at the Gallaghers, Aiden leaves Chatsworth to find his mother, recently released from prison. Mimi is unexpectedly reunited with Billy Tutton, Cilla's father, and his return to Chatsworth causes tension between Mimi and her children. Frank takes in a Polish man as a lodger. Marty and Mickey become flatmates, and both men reveal their secrets to each other.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>8</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Kevin Erlis</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/3809081.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384296827</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>388391</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>3809091</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>20</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>8</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Gordon Anderson</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Career Criminal</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>20</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2011-10-11</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Marty attempts to find a job and ends up turning to crime to tide him over. Kelly discovers that there's a price on Marty's head. Billy is determined to stand up for his rights as a father. Mimi ends up giving him an ultimatum. Mickey's flat is raided by the local police. Marty is confronted by Shane about a secret he left behind in Spain. Kelly is heartbroken agter she is told the truth and doesn't know who to believe.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>8.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>8</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Tom Higgins</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/3809091.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384296846</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>388391</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>3809101</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>21</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>8</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Lawrence Till</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>The Maguire Motto</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>21</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2011-10-18</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Mickey channels his' inner drama queen' at the community service with a difference. Ray's skill with numbers does not go unnoticed by Mickey, and a trip to the casino seems on the cards. But Ray's only got one thing on his mind, and it's not the jackpot! The community service cast are unhappy with their leader, Michelle and the play. So when Michelle has a timely accident and the centre is shut, Mickey takes the lead, bringing Christmas to Chatsworth early. Meanwhile, Mimi might wear the trousers in the family, but it's time Billy pulled his weight, so Mimi sets a profitable challenge to test his manhood. </Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>9.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>8</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Ian Kershaw</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/3809101.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384296967</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>388391</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>3809111</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>22</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>8</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>PC Gallagher</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>22</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2011-10-25</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Billy and Mimi find the game is up after Micky finds them in a compromising position. Billy is scared as the Maguire brothers want his blood for daring to marry their mother. Kelly's not sure about keeping the baby and Jamie ends up finding out more than he bargained for after he confronts her at work. Kelly realises she has to be honest with him but will he still want her and the baby. Carl sees a crime being committed but walks past, unaware of the consequences. Billy's stag ends up being a night to remember. </Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>8.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>8</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Jimmy Dowdall</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/3809111.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384296983</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>388391</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>4236854</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>1</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>9</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>The End of an Era (1)</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>1</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2012-01-09</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>The dysfunction Gallagher family returns, but all is not well on the Chatsworth Estate. Half of Frank's neighbours are evicted from their homes as part of Operation New Start, a multi-agency crackdown on the estate's benefits culture. Jamie and Karen become the reluctant leaders of the resistance when the evictees turn to them for help, but while things look bleak for everyone else, Jackson's future appears brighter than ever.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.5</Rating>
  <RatingCount>2</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>9</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/4236854.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1392925880</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>482132</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>4237390</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>2</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>9</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Save Chatsworth (2)</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>2</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2012-01-10</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Not everyone is pleased to see Carl after he shows up on the estate as a qualified policeman. Jackson finds himself being accused of falsely claiming benefits, resulting in the loss of his job which throws his marriage into chaos. Frank is given the job of becoming a double agent, so that he can get information from Carmen about the future plans for the estate. The residents end up agreeing to a deal with Carmen to save the estate. Kelly loses her baby.
</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>9.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>9</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/4237390.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1392925892</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>482132</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>4237391</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>3</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>9</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Open to  All</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>3</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2012-01-17</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Mimi and Billy decide to have an open marriage. Patty and Lillian's funeral mourning brings them some unwanted attention. Kelly can't grieve and and ends up losing control.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.5</Rating>
  <RatingCount>2</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>9</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/4237391.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1392925917</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>482132</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>4237392</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>4</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>9</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Vendetta</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>4</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2012-01-24</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Micky ends up becoming the victim of a gay bashing, leaving him mentally and physically scarred whilst enjoying a night out with the boys. Carl falls for Clem on the night out. Aidan has a new group of older friends, headed by gang leader Frasier Kane. Events end up spiraling out of control one evening on the estate and Aidan is faced with a life-changing decision. Ruby Hepburn shows up on the estate and is revealed as being Mimi's niece.
</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>8.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>9</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/4237392.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384293861</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>482132</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>4237393</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>5</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>9</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Cop Killer</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>5</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2012-01-31</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Somebody from Jamie's past arrives on the estate, looking for a favour to be returned. D.S. Brooks, is currently suspended pending some serious charges and Jamie doesn't know if he can go through with what he wants and the safety of his family ends up being in the balance. Aidan skips school after he is haunted with nightmares about his doing nothing to stop Frasier attacking his school teacher. After Frasier turns his attention to Letitia, Aidan ends up feeling like he has no choice but to act. Micky has to deal with a life-changing decision after a debt collection goes badly wrong.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>9.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>9</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/4237393.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384293827</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>482132</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>4237394</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>6</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>9</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Last Man Standing</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>6</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2012-02-07</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Jackson agrees to help Shane on a robbery job at a supermarket. Gloria's brother Dominic, a whisky preist, causes mayhem on the estate. Chesney regrets making a comment about Carl's girlfriend Clem.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.5</Rating>
  <RatingCount>2</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>9</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/4237394.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384293799</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>482132</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>4237395</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>7</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>9</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>All Fall Down</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>7</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2012-02-14</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Everyone is really worried about Kelly. Marty is still grieving about the loss of the baby, Kelly is punishing herself physically and mentally and is spiralling out of control. Karen ends up making a bet with Dom. Avril becomes worried after she sees her colleague Calum dispensing incorrect medication at the chemist.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.5</Rating>
  <RatingCount>2</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>9</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/4237395.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384293771</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>482132</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>4237396</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>8</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>9</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Blackout</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>8</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2012-02-21</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Times are difficult and Marty and Aidan attempt to redirect a power line to the Gallagher House so that they can use free electricity. The girls gather at the Maguire house and as the drink starts to flow, hidden truths are revealed. Jamie agrees to a lock in for the guys at the pub where Frank accepts the challenge to re-enact The Hare and the Tortoise. Chesney attempts to protect the shop but pushes himself too far in the process. </Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>2</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>9</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/4237396.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384293743</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>482132</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>4237397</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>9</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>9</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Decision Time</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>9</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2012-02-28</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>When Chesney arrives home from hospital, he finds his cousin Toof waiting there for him. After he reveals his plan to close the shop and take Chesney back to Bradford, Chesney refuses to agree to it. Chesney decides that it is time for him to strike out on his own and live life to the full. </Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>8.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>9</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/4237397.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384293713</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>482132</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>4237398</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>10</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>9</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Million Dollar Maguire (1)</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>10</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2012-03-06</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Jamie and Shane come up with a plan to steal a stash of scratch cards from the Lottery rooms in Manchester. Frank ends up being recruited along with Aidan and Ruby but things don't go to plan. Letitia and her friends form a girl group. Karen is determined to prove to Mimi that she can handle the Maguire business in Jamie's absence.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.5</Rating>
  <RatingCount>2</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>9</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/4237398.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1392925937</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>482132</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>4237399</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>11</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>9</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Rescue Me (2)</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>11</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2012-03-13</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Jamie is scared that Karen may uncover the truth about what happened with Gloria. Ruby wants to be accepted as part of the Maguire family while Aidan is fed up with being treated like the idiot child. </Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>8.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>9</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/4237399.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1392925947</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>482132</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>4395264</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>1</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>10</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>The Working Man (1)</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>1</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2012-09-12</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Frank's old excuses fail to wash with the Department of Work and Pensions, so faced with losing benefits his hopes rest with the World of Burgers.

Shane and Jackson launch a new enterprise of bootleg booze, but it's rank and nobody is buying their stuff. Billy offers to help and concocts a brew using his extraordinary sense of smell and amazingly it's a great success. But Shane is seriously hacked off. It's time to lay down the law...

Meanwhile, Avril supplies pills to Patty, who wants more than her recommended dosage, but when Avril turns down her request, Patty springs into action with a plan to steal them.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>10</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/4395264.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1392925966</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>500513</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>170</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>300</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>4397342</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>2</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>10</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>The World of Burger (2)</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>2</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2012-09-13</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Frank is enjoying his new job at World of Burgers. Wesley is jealous of his influence though and comes up with a scheme to oust him in order to achieve his longed-for promotion. Karen uses some alternative parenting methods to deal with Connor's destructive hobby. Mimi adopts this new approach with Cilla after hearing a few home truths. Shane's search for a missing cat leads to a new experiment.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>10</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/4397342.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1392925978</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>500513</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>4397343</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>3</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>10</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>The Brazillian Effect</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>3</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2012-09-19</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Marty befriends a Brazilian housemaid and determines to rescue her from her life of servitude. Kelly insists it's none of their business, but that doesn't deter Marty, who liberates her with a stack of cash he was supposed to be banking for Lillian...

Dom springs an uninvited guest on Gloria: their birth mother Hazel. There's no love lost between the two, but is it time for Gloria to extend the hand of friendship?

And Billy's sick of people taking advantage. Karen reckons the answer to his problems is a self-help tape.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>10</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/4397343.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384293486</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>500513</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>4397344</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>4</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>10</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Who's the Mummy?</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>4</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2012-09-26</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Billy discovers a used pregnancy test after Mimi, Karen and Gloria spend the night boozing. He turns to Jamie for advice, and both of them set out to discover who's the daddy...

Jackson is suspicious because Avril and Calum are always together after hours, but when he sneers at an invitation to go clubbing, Avril leaves him behind and makes it a night to remember.

Aiden and Chesney collect meat for a raffle and manage to get stuck with a live cow, a guilt-ridden Shane starts watching the family of the man he's killed, and Gloria turns to Dom when she gets into trouble with a loan company.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>10</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/4397344.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1392925998</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>500513</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>4397345</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>5</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>10</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>The Truth Will Out</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>5</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2012-10-03</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>Imogen Thomas</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Consumed with guilt after the hit and run, Shane tries to makes amends by befriending Ruth, the widow of the man he killed. Blind to his identity, Ruth welcomes Shane into her life, but her troubled teenage son Shaun hates this interfering stranger.

Meanwhile, Kelly and Lillian face tough competition when another brothel opens on the Chatsworth.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>10</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/4397345.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384293048</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>500513</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>4405835</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>6</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>10</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Secrets and Wives</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>6</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2012-10-10</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Marty makes a life-changing decision and finds the nerve to propose to Kelly. Over the moon, she accepts.

</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>10</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/4405835.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384292963</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>500513</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>4415032</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>7</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>10</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Business as Usual</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>7</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2012-10-17</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Shane's and Jacksons business is booming. Expansion is afoot and their future looks rosy. But Shane suddenly turns charitable and begins giving the homeless their stock, infuriating Jackson and causing a rivalry between the two business partners. Meanwhile, the residents are shocked by Patty's sudden generosity towards her neigbours. But when she begins hosting a coffee morning for the elderly, they discover a scam is afoot, and the whole estate turn against her. An outcast in the community, Patty finds her problems only just beginning when she is targeted by a hate campaign. And, Billy is having trouble in the bedroom, and a devastated Mimi is convinced he no longer loves her. </Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>10</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number>122</absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/4415032.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1392926016</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>500513</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>4417728</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>8</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>10</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>What are Friends For?</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>8</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2012-10-24</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Dom receives a disturbing text from an ex-girlfriend, who appears to be in desperation, so he turns to Frank for help. Meanwhile, Lillian discovers her girls have been servicing a judge. </Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>10</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/4417728.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1392926030</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>500513</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>4417729</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>9</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>10</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Great Rivalry</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>9</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2012-10-31</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>When a new gang hit Chatsworth, The Maguires fear for their future on the estate, and it falls on Jamie to protect his family from their new enemies. however, one of the Maguires closest friends is giving the gang inside infomation. But who? Meanwhile, Frank and Dom clash over the number of conquests they've made on the estate. </Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>10</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/4417729.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384292905</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>500513</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>4419631</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>10</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>10</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>One Year On</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>10</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2012-11-01</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>It's a big day for Mimi Maguire - it's her first wedding anniversary to Billy and they're going to renew their vows. Determined to make a fresh start, Mimi sets about throwing away memories of her past life with Paddy, but she alienates a furious Ruby with her comments about her dad.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>10</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/4419631.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384292890</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>500513</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>4506419</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>1</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>11</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Paul Norton Walker</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>The Golden Empire</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>1</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2013-02-26</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>It's a grand occasion as the residents of Chatsworth celebrate being awarded an Olympic ring from London 2012. The Maguires toast the expansion of their empire: Mimi's hijacked control of the local school via the PTA and Shane's setting up a new business venture. Business is booming, but the family is thrown into turmoil when Jamie makes a shocking discovery about his family tree and withdraws from the firm. Can Mimi persuade Jamie to return as head of the family before all is lost or will a shocking secret tear Chatsworth's leading family apart? Meanwhile, Frank finds himself climbing the employment ladder as janitor of 'St Mimi's School', conveniently funding his new leisure activity - the Gastric Bandits, a prostitute double act with Sherrilee and Derrilee, who light up his life.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>126</ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>11</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Jimmy Dowdall</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/4506419.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384292796</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>513281</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>4506420</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>2</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>11</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Dominic Leclerc</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Good Morning, Mrs Maguire</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>2</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2013-03-05</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>As a member of the PTA, Mimi demands respect. But when the teachers threaten to quit over the return of a notorious troublemaker and Mimi's quick to dole out advice, Headmaster Banbury couldn't care less. When Mimi hears that the school will be failed by School Inspector Edward Clayhill, she decides to save the day. But not without the help of the Chatsworth residents. Meanwhile, Jamie tries to contact his half-brother Kassi, but after the punch-up in the Jockey, Kassi won't pick up the phone. When Kassi fails to show for a drink, Jamie's forced to recognise that maybe having a new brother isn't going to work. Elsewhere, Frank discovers an unexpected perk of being janitor at the school: 24-hour access. Quick to take advantage, Frank invites the Gastric Bandits for an after-hours drug-fuelled romp, whilst Gloria and Dom continue to hide their sordid affair. But how long can they keep their disgraced secret?</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>127</ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>11</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Jack Lothian</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/4506420.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384292826</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>513281</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>4506421</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>3</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>11</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Daikin Marsh</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Money in Mind</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>3</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2013-03-12</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Kelly agrees to help save Lillian's savings from police survelliance. But when she discovers how much Lillian has, she is forced to decide what she values more: Money or Lillian's friendship? Meanwhile, Banbury is forced to ask Mimi for help when a problem occurs at the school. Elsewhere, Patreesha plans a housewarming party for Avril which suffers problems surrounding the theme.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>128</ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>11</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Mark Brotherhood</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/4506421.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384292845</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>513281</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>4506424</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>4</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>11</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>No-One's Perfect</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>4</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2013-03-19</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Jamie's illusion of his brother's perfect life is shattered when the police raid Kassi's home and haul him to the station. Kassi won't tell Jamie what's going on, but asks Jamie to help find him and his family a place on the Chatsworth during the investigation. So the Blanco family: Kassi, his wife Esther and their four feral children move in next door to the Maguires. Excited by their recent underhand windfall, Kelly and Marty decide to buy a house, but suspicions are aroused about their dirty money, and all hell breaks loose. Shane plays a game of cat and mouse with Sergeant Randall - a shag would suffice but Shane now wants more, and Randall likes to play by her own rules. Shane is treading a fine line - what will the Maguires say when they find out?</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>11</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/4506424.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384295149</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>513281</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>4506425</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>5</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>11</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Risky Business</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>5</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2013-03-26</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Chesney's having a rough day at work. His chillers have broken, but on the hunt for replacements he meets Remona, a feisty Muslim pharmacist. Within no time he decides to refit Chesco, add a chemist and give Remona the job of running it. But has he acted too rashly? When Avril loses her job, Patreesha insists that she goes to work at the car wash she owns with her husband, Bernard. But Patreesha is in for a shock when she investigates their business further. Elsewhere, Kassi, Shane and Jamie are suited and booted for a big night on the town, but things don't go according to plan.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>11</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/4506425.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384295179</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>513281</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>4506426</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>6</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>11</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Gordon Anderson</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Death and Erasures</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>6</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2013-04-02</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Aiden is once again in trouble with the law. Sentenced to community service, Aiden is forced to care for an OAP called Stanton. But his life is thrown into turmoil when Stanton dies whilst he was supposed to be looking after him. Meanwhile, Esther is struggled to keep her family together without Kassi. But when she reaches breaking point, Frank comes to her rescue and teaches her that life as a single-parent isn't bad. Elsewhere, Dom is convinced he is guilty of murder. But whose murder?</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>131</ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>11</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Jack Lothian</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/4506426.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384294683</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>513281</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>4506427</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>7</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>11</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Paul Norton Walker</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Crime and Punishment</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>7</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2013-04-09</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>Jason Orange</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Shane's plans for DJ Scouse Mouse at Shane-a-delica are going well. Tickets for the festival are selling out and the site looks impressive. After Mimi and Jamie learn about Shane's affair with Randall they decide they can't supply any drugs at the festival, resulting in a chain of events which puts Shane's relationship with Randall and the festival itself in jeopardy. </Overview>
  <ProductionCode>132</ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>11</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Jimmy Dowdall</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/4506427.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384294705</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>513281</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>4506428</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>8</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>11</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>David Threlfall</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Grandaddy Gallagher</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>8</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2013-04-16</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Frank is shocked when he boards a bus - only to be reunited with his eldest son, Lip, and grandaughter Katie. However, it is not a pleasent reunion between father and son as it soon becomes clear that Lip is living in the area. But doesn't want Katie to be associated with his alcoholic father or Chatsworth.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>133</ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>11</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Loren McLaughlan &amp; Amy Roberts</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/4506428.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384295019</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>513281</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>4506429</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>9</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>11</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Domesticated Specialist</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>9</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2013-04-23</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>A robbery at Chesney's shop reunites Remona with her estranged father, Barry. But she is not willing to rekindle their relationship. However, Chesney begins warming to her father and plots to reunite them. Meanwhile, Frank thinks he's hit the jackpot when he finds a stash of drugs at Esther's. Elsewhere, Shane is pushed to breaking point as Randall becomes obsessed with him.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>134</ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>11</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/4506429.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384295039</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>513281</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>4506430</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>10</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>11</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Crossing the Line</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>10</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2013-04-30</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Billy is fed up of being the village idiot and decides it's time to earn the respect of Mimi and his peers by applying for a security salesman job. But with no experience and qualifications it's not that easy. Things start to unravel when Billy pretends he's secured the job and sinks to new levels in his quest for respect. Esther is shocked to discover that Thalia's black eye is a result of her daughter being a bully. Determined to make Thalia show more compassion for her schoolmates and set a good example, Esther sets about apologising to various Chatsworth residents, but they are far from impressed. Meanwhile, Lillian takes pity on a neglected Stella and invites her to spend time in her house. A brothel is no place for a young child though, especially when she gives Lillian's valued workers nits.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>11</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/4506430.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384295102</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>513281</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>4506431</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>11</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>11</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>The P Factor</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>11</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2013-05-07</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Patreesha thinks she is the latest British music export to the States when her new jazz musician boyfriend Louis promises her a lucrative singing career across the pond. But when Louis is outed as a con-man and Patreesha's dreams become nightmares, Avril goes to extreme lengths to help get her sister out of the trouble she has put herself in. Meanwhile, a misunderstanding with Mimi leads to Frank becoming an outcast amogst the Chatsworth community. </Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>11</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/4506431.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384294814</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>513281</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>4506432</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>12</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>11</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Early Retirement</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>12</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2013-05-14</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>It seems Chatsworth may never be the same again when Mimi announces her plans to retire and move to Wilmslow to dedicate her life to charity. Is this the end of the Maguires? And will a reluctant Billy be joining her? </Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>11</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/4506432.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384294857</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>513281</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>4506433</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>13</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>11</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Kiss, Kiss, Bang, Bang</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>13</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2013-05-21</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Things are looking up for Frank: Derilee has left her husband and joined him at the Gallaghers, becoming a surrogate mum for Stella and his job is going well. However, things are set to change forever when a gunman runs riot on the estate - It's Derilee's husband Baxter and his target is Frank. As police swarm the estate, Frank, Derilee and Stella are held hostage, and if that wasn't enough for the feckless Gallagher to handle: ex-wife Monica is back! Meanwhile, Lillian has a new boyfriend, whilst Mimi's fued with the Blanco family reaches a climax.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>11</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/4506433.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384294933</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>513281</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>4506434</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>14</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>11</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>2</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>End of the Line</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>14</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2013-05-28</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>After spending months in jail, Frank returns to Chatsworth hoping for a welcome home party. However, he discovers Monica has took up residency at the Gallaghers - and is expecting his tenth child, and the return of a few faces from his past heralds the end of an era. Meanwhile, it's business as usual at Chesco's, as an old face re-instates herself.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>11</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer></Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/78846/4506434.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1384294970</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>513281</seasonid>
  <seriesid>78846</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>225</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
</Data>