<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Data><Series>
  <id>71119</id>
  <Actors>|Hilary Duff|Lalaine|Adam Lamberg|Hallie Todd|Jake Thomas|Robert Carradine|</Actors>
  <Airs_DayOfWeek>Friday</Airs_DayOfWeek>
  <Airs_Time>7:30 AM</Airs_Time>
  <ContentRating></ContentRating>
  <FirstAired>2001-01-12</FirstAired>
  <Genre>|Children|Comedy|</Genre>
  <IMDB_ID>tt0273366</IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Network>Disney Channel</Network>
  <NetworkID></NetworkID>
  <Overview>Lizzie McGuire is all about the ordinary and not-so-ordinary adventures of a junior high student and her two best friends as they try to deal… More with the ups and downs of school, popularity, boys, parents, a bratty little brother--just life in general. And if Lizzie leaves anything unsaid, you can bet that her cartoon alter ego will say it for her!</Overview>
  <Rating>7.3</Rating>
  <RatingCount>4</RatingCount>
  <Runtime>30</Runtime>
  <SeriesID>1229</SeriesID>
  <SeriesName>Lizzie McGuire</SeriesName>
  <Status>Ended</Status>
  <added></added>
  <addedBy></addedBy>
  <banner>graphical/71119-g3.jpg</banner>
  <fanart>fanart/original/71119-5.jpg</fanart>
  <lastupdated>1432528189</lastupdated>
  <poster>posters/71119-1.jpg</poster>
  <tms_wanted_old>1</tms_wanted_old>
  <zap2it_id>SH413310</zap2it_id>
</Series>
<Episode>
  <id>1164201</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>1</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>0</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Jim Fall</Director>
  <EpImgFlag></EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>The Lizzie McGuire Movie</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>1</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2003-05-02</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Lizzie embarks on a school trip to Italy, where she discovers she looks exactly like one of the country's most famous pop stars. She agrees to stand in for the performer at an awards ceremony, but the deception is complicated when she falls for her double's singing partner.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode></ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>0</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Susan Estelle Jansen|Ed Decter|John J. Strauss|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <airsafter_season></airsafter_season>
  <airsbefore_episode></airsbefore_episode>
  <airsbefore_season></airsbefore_season>
  <filename></filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196427</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>18587</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height></thumb_height>
  <thumb_width></thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34776</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>3.0</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber>3.0</DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season>1</DVD_season>
  <Director>Neal Israel</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Rumors</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>1</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2001-01-12</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Byron Fox|Taylor Gunnin|Mitchah Williams|Britney Mitchell|Melissa Matthews|Tiffany Burton|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Lizzie tries out for cheerleader but doesn't do very well. Later that night she and Miranda chat online. Lizzie jokes that Kate made the squad because she stuffs her bra. Miranda accidentally sends out the message to everyone on the class roster. The next day at school Kate is furious about the taunting she's receiving and confronts Lizzie and Miranda, demanding to know who is responsible. Lizzie stutters and stammers for a few moments, then Miranda says that she did it. Kate promises to make her life miserable, and a war of dirty tricks breaks out between the two. Miranda tells Lizzie that she took the blame because Lizzie can't handle conflict. Lizzie feels guilty as the war between Miranda and Kate escalates. Finally Lizzie works up the nerve to take responsibilty for the message and she stands up to Kate. Also, Matt brings home a lizard for a school project and names it Lizzie, much to his sister's annoyance. While Mr. and Mrs. McGuire are supposed to be watching the lizard, it die</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>103</ProductionCode>
  <Rating>7.0</Rating>
  <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Melissa Gould</Writer>
  <absolute_number>3</absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34776.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196405</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1682</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34777</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>2.0</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber>2.0</DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season>1</DVD_season>
  <Director>Neal Israel</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Picture Day</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>2</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2001-01-19</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Sonya Eddy|Aaron Fors|Chelsea J. Wilson|Clayton Snyder|Amy Fuzzell|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Lizzie, Miranda and Gordo all have big problems on the day their pictures are to be taken for the junior high yearbook. Lizzie searches and searches for the right thing to wear, but her mother insists she put on a &quot;&quot;hideous&quot;&quot; sweater that her grandmother gave her. Miranda runs afoul of Kate when they both show up wearing the same outfit. And Gordo feels the pressure to assume a tough-guy pose when his picture is snapped. Meanwhile Matt hasn't studied for a quiz at school, so he fakes being sick to get out of it. But he finds out that his mom's cure can be worse than the disease.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>102</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Douglas Tuber|Tim Maile|</Writer>
  <absolute_number>2</absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34777.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196213</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1682</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34778</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>5.0</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber>5.0</DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season>1</DVD_season>
  <Director>Mark Rosman</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>When Moms Attack</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>3</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2001-01-26</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Craig Anton|Byron Fox|Clayton Snyder|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Lizzie is looking forward to the science class field trip, but she is mortified when she finds out that her mother is a last-minute replacement as the girls' chaperone. Lizzie fears that her mother will embarrass her to death, and Mom does a pretty good job of doing just that while they are competing with the boys on a nature walk. But Mrs. McGuire proves how cool she can be when she helps the girls get back at the boys for a prank they pulled then takes all the blame herself. Back at home, Matt and Mr. McGuire are left on their own and try to cook for themselves.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>105</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Nina G. Bargiel|Jeremy J. Bargiel|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34778.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196116</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1682</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34779</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>1.0</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber>1.0</DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season>1</DVD_season>
  <Director>Larry Shaw</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Pool Party (Pilot)</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>4</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2001-02-02</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Dot Jones|Byron Fox|Jennifer Freeman|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Lizzie and Miranda are ecstatic about being invited to a pool party given by their heartthrob, Danny Kessler. Mrs. McGuire is excited for Lizzie too until she finds out it's on the same day as grandma's 80th birthday party. She tells Lizzie she has to go to her grandma's instead and Lizzie is furious. The next day at school Miranda temporarily gets on the good side of Kate, the girls' former best friend who has literally and figuratively outgrown them. Kate invites Miranda to hang out with her crowd, causing a conflict between Miranda and Lizzie. At home Lizzie catches her mom on the phone making up a lie to get out of a commitment and accuses her of being a hypocrite. Gordo helps Lizzie to smooth over her differences with Miranda. Mom tells Lizzie she can go to the party after all, but she decides not to and spends the day with Gordo.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>101</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Terri Minsky</Writer>
  <absolute_number>1</absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34779.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431931908</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1682</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34780</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>4.0</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber>4.0</DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season>1</DVD_season>
  <Director>Alan Myerson</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>I've Got Rhythmic</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>5</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2001-02-09</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Dot Jones|Brianna James|Michael Barryte|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Lizzie is dissatisfied with being an ordinary &quot;&quot;B&quot;&quot; student and is looking for something at which she can excel. Surprisingly, she finds out in gym class that she has a real talent for rhythmic gymnastics. But she thinks the sport is stupid and is ambivalent about competing. She trains hard and goes to the regional competition, where a jealous Kate tries to sabotage her performance. Miranda and Gordo help foil Kate's plan and Lizzie wins first place. Her parents are proud but Lizzie decides to give up the sport and go back to being her &quot;&quot;ordinary&quot;&quot; self.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>104</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Nancy Neufeld Callaway</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34780.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196366</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1682</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34781</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>6.0</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber>6.0</DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season>1</DVD_season>
  <Director>Savage Steve Holland</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Jack of All Trades</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>6</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2001-02-23</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>Craig Anton</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Gordo is sure that Mr. Pettus is giving him &quot;&quot;B&quot;&quot;s instead of &quot;&quot;A&quot;&quot;s because Pettus doesn't like him. His state of mind isn't helped any when the teacher gives the class an aptitude test which shows that Gordo is best suited to be a blackjack dealer. To prove that Mr. Pettus has it in for him, Gordo convinces Lizzie to turn in his science project with her name on it and vice versa, which ends up having disasterous results. Also, Matt adopts a hip-hop attitude and insists that everyone call him &quot;&quot;M-Dogg.&quot;&quot;</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>106</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Trish Baker</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34781.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196454</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1682</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34782</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>18.0</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber>18.0</DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season>1</DVD_season>
  <Director>Savage Steve Holland</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Aaron Carter's Coming to Town (aka Here Comes Aaron Carter)</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>7</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2001-03-23</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Aaron Carter|Brad Grunberg|David Alex Rosen|Angela Oh|Gregory Hinton|Rory J. Shoaf|Nonny Price|Nikole Smith|Nicole Neil|Allison Kyler|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Lizzie and Miranda are excited about the news that singer Aaron Carter is coming to their town to do a video shoot. They enlist Gordo to help them figure out where the shoot will take place so they can crash the set and meet Aaron. Matt horns his way into the group also. When they arrive at the site Matt is mistaken for Aaron's stand-in and let on the set, but the other three are not. They try several ways to sneak in but are always chased off by a security guard. In all the confusion Mr. and Mrs. McGuire somehow manage to get detained by security. Aaron's manager catches the trio and Lizzie convinces her to at least let one of them meet Aaron. She agrees, and Lizzie tells Miranda that she can be the one. Lizzie goes back to get a tape recorder she left behind and runs in to Aaron, who gives her a kiss. The kids all get to be extras in the video.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>118</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Nina G. Bargiel|Jeremy J. Bargiel|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34782.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196339</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1682</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34783</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>7.0</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber>7.0</DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season>1</DVD_season>
  <Director>Mark Rosman</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Misadventures in Babysitting</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>8</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2001-04-06</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Diana Weng|Randy McPherson|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>When a babysitter cancels on the McGuires, Lizzie suggests that she's old enough to do the job for her brother Matt, but mom and dad say no. After much persuasion from Lizzie they relent, and Miranda and Gordo also come over to help. After Mr. and Mrs. McGuire leave, Matt generally causes havoc, spilling grape juice on the rug, acting bratty and taking advantage of Lizzie, who badly wants to impress her parents with her responsibility. Miranda and Gordo aren't much help as they won't follow Lizzie's orders either. At the restaurant Sam McGuire wants to sneak home and check on his daughter and son; Jo doesn't like the idea, but says just don't let them see you. Meanwhile at the house, Matt has knocked out the power. Mr. McGuire tries to peer in the window and goes tumbling over. The kids think he's a burglar and call the police. Mr. McGuire tries to get in the locked house and the kids wage a battle against him reminiscent of the movie Home Alone. The police come to arrest Sam. After al</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>107</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|David Blum|Stacy Kramer|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34783.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196389</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1682</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34784</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>8.0</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber>8.0</DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season>1</DVD_season>
  <Director>Brian K. Roberts</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Election</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>9</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2001-04-20</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Sara Paxton|Bernard Kira|Cory Hodges|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Lizzie and friends are frustrated--the only candidates for school president are super-popular cheerleader Claire Miller and oddball Larry Tudgeman, who promises to eat a worm for every vote he gets. Gordo encourages Lizzie to run as a &quot;&quot;normal&quot;&quot; candidate and Miranda seconds the motion. Lizzie agrees to do it. Gordo is her gung-ho campaign manager as she runs on a &quot;&quot;voice of the people&quot;&quot; platform. Lizzie starts to gain confidence, even enough to tell off Claire and Kate. Gordo thinks she should schmooze the &quot;&quot;second-tier&quot;&quot; popular kids in the drama club, so Lizzie puts on her shades and black leather and tries to get in good with them. Miranda is annoyed that Lizzie is blowing off the less popular kids and groups to hang with the drama club. Lizzie starts to develop a prima donna attitude and now Gordo has to agree that he has helped create a monster in candidate Lizzie. The big surprise on election day is that underdog Larry wins. Lizzie must face Miranda and Gordo after the election but th</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>108</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Melissa Gould</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34784.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196198</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1682</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34785</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>9.0</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber>9.0</DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season>1</DVD_season>
  <Director>Steve DeJarnatt</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>I Do, I Don't</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>10</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2001-04-27</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Candy Brown Houston|Chelsea J. Wilson|Mitchah Williams|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Mrs. Stebel pairs up the students in her social studies class for a mock marriage assignment. Each set of partners must draw a job from a jar at random, work up a fictional lifestyle and report back at a pretend 20-year reunion. Always-snobby Kate is horrified to find herself matched up with Larry Tudgeman, but at least she likes her job, a television anchorwoman. Lizzie wants to be partnered with Ethan Craft, who's not so smart but is cute. But she gets familiar old Gordo, whose job is sanitation engineer (garbageman). Lizzie figures it's not so bad, though, since Gordo will probably ensure she gets a good grade. Her mind begins to change when Miranda gets picked to be Ethan's partner, and he's a surgeon to boot. Lizzie can't help but be jealous.
Kate tries to completely ignore her &quot;&quot;husband&quot;&quot; Larry, and Lizzie unconsciously does the same thing to Gordo, as she begins obsessing about Ethan and Miranda, who couldn't be happier. Gordo is disappointed that his friend Lizzie is taking him f</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>109</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Nina G. Bargiel|Jeremy J. Bargiel|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34785.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196135</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1682</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34786</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>10.0</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber>10.0</DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season>1</DVD_season>
  <Director>Anson Williams</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Bad Girl McGuire</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>11</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2001-05-04</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Jackie Angelescu|Page Leong|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>In math class, punked-out troublemaker Angel puts gums in Lizzie's hair, then tries to cheat off her test paper. The teacher is annoyed with the distractions and sends them both to detention. Lizzie is nervous about entering the detention hall for the first time and facing Angel again, but she actually finds that the experience is a different one for her--almost fun.  When she gets home, Mom is mad at her for not calling about being late. Lizzie lies about where she's been. Mom is also mad at Matt for being late. When he complains about the freedoms his friends have, including no bedtimes, Mom makes a deal: if he comes home on time, he won't have a bedtime. Matt is overjoyed about this, but Jo seems to know what she's doing.
At school Lizzie is now dressing like Angel and hanging with her. She's also forging notes and cutting classes. Angel invites her to a high-school party on Friday. When Lizzie later finds out there will be no parents at the party, she's secretly worried. Gordo and</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>110</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Melissa Gould</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34786.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196107</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1682</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34787</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>11.0</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber>11.0</DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season>1</DVD_season>
  <Director>Mark Rosman</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Between a Rock and a Bra Place</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>12</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2001-05-11</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|David Carradine|Ty Upshaw|Amelia Marshall|Dana Pauley|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Lizzie and Miranda note that when a girl gets her first bra, her personality somehow seems to change. They decide they are ready for their first, and hatch a plan to get Lizzie's mom to take them to the mall where they will shop for &quot;&quot;school supplies.&quot;&quot; Lizzie is a terrible liar, though, and blurts out the real reason for the trip. Mom is overjoyed to help the girls out, but she embarrasses them as they are shopping. Lizzie is very harsh with her mother, telling her that she and Miranda are old enough to do their own shopping and to leave them alone. The girls face further embarrassment when they run into Kate, Claire, and their English teacher Mr. Coppersmith. They also find that they don't know what to look for. They find Mrs. McGuire and apologize for being abrupt with her and ask for her help. Also, Matt is entering the Jet Li sidekick contest. He gets his dad and Gordo with his camcorder to help him make a martial arts movie as his contest entry, but it doesn't go well. Sam McGuire</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>111</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Nina G. Bargiel|Jeremy J. Bargiel|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34787.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196037</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1682</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34788</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>12.0</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber>12.0</DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season>1</DVD_season>
  <Director>Timothy Busfield</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Come Fly with Me</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>13</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2001-06-01</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>Bernard Kira</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Gordo, always the nonconformist, has a new passion: 1950s &amp; '60s Las Vegas lounge culture, as epitomized by Frank Sinatra and the &quot;&quot;Rat Pack.&quot;&quot; Lizzie and Miranda don't care for it, but they buy Gordo a Rat Pack CD. Ethan Craft listens to it on the bus and, surprisingly, likes it, which makes the girls reconsider their opinion. Soon they are dressing in fashions of the time. Gordo thinks it's cool that they like it, but hopes that his new interest won't become the latest passing fad at school. But that looks like exactly what is happening as Ethan soon has all the guys wearing hats like Sinatra and listening to the music. Even Kate is admiring the girls for being in first on the new trend and actually asks for their advice on what to do!
Gordo starts to sour on the Rat Pack and he comes up with a new interest--radio-controlled 1/64 scale World War II airplanes, only his enthusiasm doesn't seem genuine. Committee chairman Kate plans the theme for the next dance, &quot;&quot;Lounging Around.&quot;&quot; She put</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>112</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Douglas Tuber|Tim Maile|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34788.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196277</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1682</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34789</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>13.0</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber>13.0</DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season>1</DVD_season>
  <Director>Steve DeJarnatt</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Random Acts of Miranda</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>14</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2001-06-08</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Orlando Brown|Troy Rowland|Mitchah Williams|Ryan Shannon|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Lizzie, who is writing for the school newspaper, asks for the assignment of covering the school's production of Mr. Escobar's play &quot;&quot;Greasier.&quot;&quot; Miranda is overjoyed when she unexpectedly gets the lead in the play. When Lizzie and Gordo go to rehearsal, however, they are dismayed to find that Miranda is a terrible actress, and clumsy to boot. Miranda is confident before the opening of the play, but her performance is no better and she destroys most of the props and scenery. Lizzie can't bring herself to write the bad review Miranda deserves, but Gordo thinks she'll  be able to take it. Lizzie writes a review that is honest, but goes easy on Miranda. Her friend doesn't see it that way, though, and thinks Lizzie has betrayed her. At lunch they get into a big fight. Gordo gives Miranda a tape of her performance and a copy of Lizzie's review and asks her to watch and read them both. Lizzie writes a retraction of her review but Miranda now realizes she was just being honest and tells her not</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>113</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Douglas Tuber|Tim Maile|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34789.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196253</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1682</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34790</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>14.0</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber>14.0</DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season>1</DVD_season>
  <Director>Jace Alexander</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Lizzie's Nightmares</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>15</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2001-06-22</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Phill Lewis|Tony Jones|Randy McPherson|Hayk Kalantarian|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Lizzie is in a frenzy because Ethan Craft has asked her to sit with him at lunch the next day. But at home she still has to put up with bratty brother Matt, who put honey on the phone receiver and messed up her hair. Lizzie is furious with him and this time his parents are also very upset, too. They ground him and Mom says there will be more severe punishment to come. Matt races to catch the bus, but he gets on the wrong one, the junior high bus. Ethan Craft tells him to get out of his seat, but Matt stands up to him, which Ethan likes. He tells him his name is &quot;&quot;Bond...Matt Bond.&quot;&quot; By the time they reach school, Matt has  created a legend for himself as a child prodigy, actor, etc. and his reputation has already spread all over school.
At home, Jo McGuire is worried when she hears Matt isn't at school. She fears he may have run away because she and husband Sam were so harsh with him. They call the police and even try to get Lanny to talk. Meanwhile, Lizzie heads toward Ethan's lunch tab</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>114</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Melissa Gould</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34790.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196043</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1682</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34791</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>16.0</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber>16.0</DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season>1</DVD_season>
  <Director>Savage Steve Holland</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Obsession</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>16</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2001-06-29</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Sybyl Walker|Chelsea J. Wilson|Lawrence Mandley|Troy Rowland|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>The various obsessions of Lizzie, Matt and Gordo are driving friends, family, teachers and themselves to distraction. Gordo is intent on winning the Science Olympics at all costs against defending champion Larry Tudgeman. Matt becomes hall monitor at his school and gets carried away with his own power, giving out citations to schoolmates by the dozen and even trying to do the same to teachers and family members. Meanwhile, after she and Miranda work on a successful volunteer project at school, Lizzie becomes an environmental warrior, a fanatic for collecting clothing and food for the homeless, and even a vegetarian! All three learn that they must put limits on their fanaticism or else their original causes will suffer as a result.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>116</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Nina G. Bargiel|Jeremy J. Bargiel|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34791.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196284</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1682</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34792</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>19.0</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber>19.0</DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season>1</DVD_season>
  <Director>Mark Rosman</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Sibling Bonds</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>17</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2001-08-03</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>Paul Robert Langdon</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Matt is irritating Lizzie with his magic tricks while she's trying to do homework. Soon they are fighting like cats and dogs--or brother and sister--much to the annoyance of their parents. But as soon as Sam and Jo stop them, they go right back to fighting.
At school Ethan Craft speaks to Lizzie and Miranda, but Lizzie is so tongue-tied she can barely utter a word. Mr. Escobar announces a charity drive and asks for volunteers. Lizzie thinks she'll be too busy until she hears that Ethan will be there. At home Lizzie is making some cookies for the event when Matt tries out another trick. This time he handcuffs himself to his sister, but he can't get the cuffs loose. Mom spies the key and hides it, thinking that if the kids are forced to spend a few hours chained together, they might learn to get along better. Now Lizzie is facing the horror of going to the charity drive with her little brother stuck on her arm!
At the drive, Lizzie tries to hide Matt as best she can while Kate takes adva</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>119</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Douglas Tuber|Tim Maile|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34792.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196354</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1682</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34793</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>21.0</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber>21.0</DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season>1</DVD_season>
  <Director>Peter Montgomery</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Rated Aargh</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>18</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2001-08-10</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Dot Jones|Mitchah Williams|DeVaughn Nixon|David Alex Rosen|Yolanda Laverde|Jeremy J. Bargiel|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Lizzie's fantasy almost comes true when she is paired up with Ethan Craft in a CPR class at school, but he's so dense that the teacher chooses Tudgeman instead to give Lizzie mouth-to-mouth! Lizzie, Gordo and Miranda realize they are about the only three in school who haven't seen the latest blockbuster movie Vesuvius: The Eruption, which is rated R, and they're determined to get in to see it. When their parents all say &quot;&quot;no&quot;&quot; to their arguments, Gordo decides they should say they are going to play miniature golf, then go see the film. Lizzie is very nervous about lying to her parents, but she pulls it off with ease.
The trio can't get past the ticket-taker, though, and can't slip in the back, so they mingle with the crowd as it is departing a showing and sneak in that way. While at the concession stand, they notice a man choking. Lizzie has had the training, so she goes and performs the Heimlich maneuver on the man, dislodging a sourball from his throat. A local news crew comes by and f</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>121</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Trish Baker</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34793.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196065</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1682</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34794</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>20.0</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber>20.0</DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season>1</DVD_season>
  <Director>Kim Friedman</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Gordo and the Girl</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>19</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2001-08-17</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Kyla Pratt|Carlos Alazraqui|Armando Molina|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Gordo begs off going to the horror movie marathon with Lizzie and Miranda, saying that he'll be spending some time &quot;&quot;bonding&quot;&quot; with his father. But at the Digital Bean before the show, the girls see him with Brooke Baker. At first they don't think he's on a date because he didn't tell them about it, but then they see him kiss Brooke! The girls aren't sure what to think about this. The next day at school, Gordo tells Lizzie he was with his father the day before. When he skips lunch with Lizzie and Miranda to help a &quot;&quot;friend&quot;&quot; with homework, the girls are even more confused. They just can't picture their longtime friend as anyone's boyfriend. Later, when Gordo is about to tell the girls about Brooke, Lizzie tells him first that she thinks Brooke is using him and that she's hurt he didn't tell her about his girlfriend before now. Gordo, for his part, is upset with Lizzie and Miranda for reacting the way they do.
Miranda becomes more accepting of the idea of Gordo having a girlfriend, but Lizz</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>120</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Melissa Gould</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34794.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196071</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1682</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34795</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>22.0</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber>22.0</DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season>1</DVD_season>
  <Director>Mark Rosman</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Educating Ethan</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>20</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2001-08-24</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Norma Michaels|Sebastian Jude|Amanda Oshita|Katina Waters|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Gordo wants to raise money for a new stereo, so Miranda and Lizzie suggest he tutor students who need help in math. His first student is Ethan Craft, much to the girls' delight. When Gordo is working with Ethan at the Digital Bean, Lizzie and Miranda keep trying to horn in on the action and end up spilling drinks all over the guys' papers. Gordo gets mad at them and suggests that they aren't smart enough to help him tutor anyway. The girls get angry right back at him and leave. Meanwhile, Matt and his friend Oscar are looking for something exciting to do. They decide to become &quot;&quot;super heroes&quot;&quot; Matt Man and the Incredible Oscar. They go around the neighborhood in costume trying to do good deeds, but all they do is annoy the neighbors.
At lunch the next day, Gordo is having trouble explaining fractions to Ethan. As a peace offering, Lizzie tries to help. Gordo is not too happy about it, especially when Lizzie's explanation is clearer than his own. Ethan asks Lizzie to tutor him instead. Li</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>122</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Nina G. Bargiel|Jeremy J. Bargiel|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34795.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196318</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1682</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34796</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>23.0</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber>23.0</DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season>1</DVD_season>
  <Director>Ellen Falcon</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Lizzie Strikes Out</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>21</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2001-08-31</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>Paul Robert Langdon</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Ethan invites Lizzie, Gordo and Miranda to go bowling with friends on the weekend. Of course the girls are thrilled but Gordo isn't so happy--bowling is something he's not good at. In fact, he got so nervous doing it before that his fingers swelled up and the ball had to be cut off his hand! Miranda says she will be Gordo's &quot;&quot;life coach&quot;&quot; for bowling and tries to teach him him a kind of mystical philosophy (&quot;&quot;Be the ball!&quot;&quot;) Meanwhile, Matt and Lanny are trying to think of what they can do to stop the bully Heywood Biggs from picking on them.
When Sam McGuire hears Lizzie talking about her sort-of date on the phone, he worries that he's not involved enough in his daughter's life. He asks her if she'd like for just the two of them to go out to dinner on Friday so they can spend some time together. Lizzie agrees, but later realizes that the bowling date is the same night! She decides she'll have to ask her father to reschedule.
Lizzie explains to her dad about the bowling and he agrees to po</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>123</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Melissa Gould</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34796.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196422</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1682</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34797</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>28.0</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber>28.0</DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season>1</DVD_season>
  <Director>Anson Williams</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>The Untitled Stan Jansen Project</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>22</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2001-09-21</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Sean Hogan|Carly Schroeder|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Director Stan Jansen is filming a documentary at the junior high and everyone is trying to get on camera--except Gordo, who wants to be a director himself. But Stan singles out Gordo as his star and tells him his appearance in the film could lead to a career in directing. Gordo is eager to go along, so when the director tells him he wants conflict, Gordo trashes Kate on camera. Lizzie and Miranda think that's great, but it's not so great when Tudgeman gets upset after the same treatment. Then when Gordo manipulates Lizzie and Miranda into revealing long-held secrets about each other, the trio's friendship is on the rocks. The girls can't stay mad at each other, though, and they convince Gordo that their friendship should be the most important thing to all of them. The kids find a way to get back at Stan Jansen.
Meanwhile, Matt's classmate Melina is a real troublemaker--something he can appreciate. She's so good at it that she manages to get Matt blamed for every bad thing she does. Des</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>128</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Nina G. Bargiel|Jeremy J. Bargiel|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34797.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196093</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1682</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34798</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>24.0</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber>24.0</DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season>1</DVD_season>
  <Director>Savage Steve Holland</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Last Year's Model</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>23</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2001-09-28</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Arvie Lowe Jr.|Elizabeth Densmore|John Allsopp|Traci Melchor|Stacey Haglund|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Lizzie auditions to be in a fashion show presented by &quot;&quot;Teen Attitude&quot;&quot; magazine at a local mall and she gets accepted. At the show Lizzie looks great on the stage. Afterward, popular girl Jessica asks Lizzie to come to a party at her country club. Lizzie gets Miranda and Gordo invited also. At the party, all three are enjoying the fun, including the hot tub. But already Lizzie's friends are acting different. When Jessica asks her about coming to another party, Miranda starts answering for Lizzie like a press agent and she and Gordo start negotiating future appearances for her like a supermodel!
At school things are very different, also. Kids stare at her in the hall like she's a celebrity. Kate is now fawning all over Lizzie, wanting to be her friend. Ethan is so starstruck that he can't even mumble a coherent sentence around her. Gordo and Miranda are as bad as anybody. Lizzie muses, &quot;&quot;Gordo and Miranda aren't my friends anymore. They're my people!&quot;&quot;
Overwhelmed by the attention, Lizzie</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>124</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Douglas Tuber|Tim Maile|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34798.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196143</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1682</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34799</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>15.0</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber>15.0</DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season>1</DVD_season>
  <Director>Brian K. Roberts</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Night of the Day of the Dead</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>24</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2001-10-05</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Dyana Ortelli|Armando Molina|Korben Akira|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>The middle school is putting on a big Fright Night celebration for Halloween. Lizzie wants to appear as Vampira, the dungeon mistress, but Kate is in charge and she keeps the job for herself, making Lizzie clean out the janitor's closet and then giving her the role of a clown handing out balloons. Miranda brings her parents, who are helping her celebrate a Mexican holiday, the Day of the Dead. They bring by several items including skulls and skeletons which are meant to represent ancestors who are being honored. Kate is all smiles when Miranda's parents are around (&quot;&quot;Toon Lizzie&quot;&quot; calls Kate &quot;&quot;phonier than cafeteria cheese&quot;&quot;), but once they leave she yells at Miranda to get rid of that junk they brought. Miranda warns Kate that by disrespecting the dead, she is risking their wrath.
Strange things begin to happen at Fright Night. The skeletons disappear, and so does Matt (dressed as himself turned inside out!), leaving behind only a handful of dirt! Gordo is gone too, but his voice is comin</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>115</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Douglas Tuber|Tim Maile|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34799.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196155</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1682</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34800</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>26.0</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber>26.0</DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season>1</DVD_season>
  <Director>Mark Rosman</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Facts of Life</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>25</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2001-10-12</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Arvie Lowe Jr.|Rick Marotta|Ivy Withrow|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Hoping to win a trip to Miami, Lizzie, Miranda and Gordo team up to enter the school's &quot;&quot;Fact-athlon.&quot;&quot; Their rival team consists of Kate Sanders, Larry Tudgeman and Claire Miller. But things start to look a little bleak when the faculty advisor Lizzie and company chose is replaced by substitute teacher Mr. Dig. But to their surprise, Mr. Dig manages to turn studying into something fun and interesting with his unusual approaches. By the time the competition starts, Lizzie's team is confident while Kate, Larry and Claire are feeling the pressure. But Kate's team beats Lizzie's team badly when there are too many questions about dates and names rather than &quot;&quot;how and why&quot;&quot; problems. Kate and her teammates gloat over their win and Mr. Dig is ready to leave his job at the school because he thinks he let the team down, But Lizzie, Gordo and Miranda convince him they they actually did learn a lot and that they had a good time doing it. Kate, Claire and Larry return from Miami limping, bugbit and s</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>126</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Douglas Tuber|Tim Maile|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34800.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196086</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1682</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34801</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>27.0</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber>27.0</DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season>1</DVD_season>
  <Director>Steve DeJarnatt</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Scarlett Larry</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>26</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2001-11-09</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Dot Jones|Jaimie Ryan|Kevin Jackson|Shawn Lane|Josh Kemble|Julie Adair|Nancy Thurston|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Lizzie finds out in square-dancing class that a guy has a crush on her--but it's Larry Tudgeman! She asks her mom's advice about how to get rid of him, but Mom suggests she find out what he's all about first, intimating that her dad was kind of a geek when she first met him. This isn't what Lizzie wants to hear, but she doesn't want to be mean and consents to go out with Larry. To her surprise, he shows up for the date looking very nice, and--bigger surprise--she actually has fun on their trip to the science museum.
Still, Lizzie doesn't want to be Larry's girlfriend, but at school the next day, Larry assumes that she is. The situation isn't helped when Kate broadcasts to the whole school that Lizzie and Larry are an item. After talking to Miranda and Gordo, Lizzie decides to let Larry down easy. After a day of letting him act like her boyfriend, Lizzie tells Larry that she doesn't think they are right for each other. Unexpectedly, he agrees, but tells Lizzie she's &quot;&quot;the nicest person I</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>127</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Amy Engelberg|Wendy Engelberg|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34801.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196171</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1682</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34802</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>29.0</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber>29.0</DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season>1</DVD_season>
  <Director>Savage Steve Holland</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Gordo and the Dwarves</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>27</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2001-11-16</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Dyana Ortelli|Armando Molina|Cory Hodges|Andrew James Allen|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Gammy McGuire sends Lizzie one of her frequent &quot;birthday&quot; gifts--a role-playing game called Dwarflord: The Conquest. Mom insists that Lizzie play it at least once, so she recruits reluctant Miranda and Gordo for a game. The girls can't understand the incredibly complex rules but Gordo likes it. In fact, Gordo joins a &quot;&quot;Dwarf Tribe&quot;&quot; at school (led by Tudgeman, of course) and begins to spend all his time playing and thinking about the game. Gordo gets so obsessed that he even quits studying and, unbelievably, gets an &quot;&quot;F&quot;&quot; on a test!
Lizzie and Miranda try to talk some sense back into Gordo but he refuses to see he is addicted to the game. Matt agrees to help the girls capture Gordo and help to deprogram him. They stealthily invade a Dwarflord game, abduct Gordo and hold an intervention in which they finally convince him to go back to his old lifestyle.
Also, Matt has to observe wildlife for a school project. His dad Sam helps him out by climbing up a tree with him to look at a bird's nest.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>129</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Douglas Tuber|Tim Maile|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34802.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196204</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1682</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34803</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>31.0</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber>31.0</DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season>1</DVD_season>
  <Director>Savage Steve Holland</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Lizzie and Kate's Big Adventure (aka Lizzie and Kate's Excellent Adventure)</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>28</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2001-11-30</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Sebastian Jude|Craig Anton|Mitchah Williams|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Gordo and Miranda visit Lizzie after she was out sick and bring her some scary news--in social studies class she has to pair up on a project with---KATE!! Lizzie reacts hysterically. She tries to get out of going to class the next day but her parents make her go. Kate is mad about working with Lizzie also, but she comes by the McGuire house to work on their project, cooking a Latvian dish called an Alexander Tort (a raspberry pastry ). At first the two are hostile to each other, but eventually they have a laugh or two and begin to recall the days when they were friends. Jo McGuire sees them enjoying themselves and tells the girls it seems like old times. Suddenly the girls stop being so friendly, then Kate excuses herself and leaves.
At school Miranda and Gordo ask Lizzie how it went with Kate, expecting the worst. Lizzie says it wasn't so bad. In fact, the two are going to the Digital Bean to do work on a high-speed computer. When they get there, Kate and Lizzie are working fine, but</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>131</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Jeremy J. Bargiel|Nina G. Bargiel|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34803.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196360</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1682</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34804</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>25.0</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber>25.0</DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season>1</DVD_season>
  <Director>Steve DeJarnatt</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>The Courtship of Miranda Sanchez</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>29</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2001-12-07</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>Shan Elliot</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>When Miranda falls head over heels for Ryan Adams after seeing him perform in drama class, Lizzie vows to do all she can to get them together. But when Miranda gets tongue-tied after meeting Ryan in the halls, she wants Lizzie to tell her exactly what she should say to him. At lunch, Lizzie hides in a garbage can and feeds lines to Miranda as she talks to Ryan. Miranda repeats everything exactly, even sneezing when Lizzie does. A bee stings Lizzie and puts an end to the charade. Miranda is disappointed after this escapade and is about ready to give up on Ryan. When Lizzie tries to explain things to Ryan, he gets it backwards and thinks Lizzie is the one who likes him and that Miranda was talking to him for her friend's sake. Miranda thinks Lizzie betrayed her. But when Lizzie makes her come along and talk to Ryan one more time, Miranda realizes she was attracted to the actor rather than the real boy and she and Lizzie make up.
Meanwhile, Gordo is getting tired of all the &quot;&quot;girl talk&quot;&quot; an</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>125</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Melissa Gould</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34804.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196332</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1682</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34805</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>17.0</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber>17.0</DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season>1</DVD_season>
  <Director>Steve DeJarnatt</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Gordo's Video</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>30</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2002-01-01</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Jeffrey Meng|Haylie Duff|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Gordo has his camera and is filming Lizzie and Miranda in the school cafeteria. He forgets the camera when they leave, and when he goes back for it, he finds it was running the whole time. When the friends view the footage, they see Kate telling Claire a big secret--she's fourteen, a year older than the other seventh graders, because she was held back in kindergarten! This gives Gordo an idea. He sets up several hidden cameras around the school which catch lots of embarrassing moments on tape. Gordo plans to make a movie and enter it in a local competition, hoping to prove with it that even the popular kids have things to be embarrassed about.
Miranda is having a bad day, and at lunch she complains to Lizzie about the school and the people in it. Unknown to them, Gordo's hidden camera filmed them. When Miranda finds out Gordo intends to use her footage in his film, Miranda is outraged. Lizzie is caught right in the middle between her two friends, both of whom expect her support. But wh</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>117</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Kris Lowe</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34805.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196029</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1682</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34806</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>30.0</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>1</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber>30.0</DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season>1</DVD_season>
  <Director>Anson Williams</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Gordo's Bar Mitzvah</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>31</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2002-01-18</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Michael Mantell|Alison Martin|Armando Molina|Dyana Ortelli|Pat Crawford Brown|Mickey Jones|Frank Sotonoma Salsedo|David Alex Rosen|Jeremy J. Bargiel|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Gordo is feeling a little left behind: the girls are going crazy over Ethan Craft, who gets a new dirtbike for his 14th birthday, just like all the &quot;&quot;men&quot;&quot; in his family have. Even Larry Tudgeman is shaving now, though not very well! Gordo now wishes he had celebrated his bar mitzvah, the Jewish ceremony performed on the 13th birthday that marks the passage of a boy into manhood. Concerned about what makes a boy a man, Gordo takes his camera interviews many different men to get their experiences. He tries several different &quot;&quot;manly&quot;&quot; things that they mentioned, even going to a tattoo parlor! But he decides they are not for him. He asks his parents why they didn't insist on a bar mitzvah for him. They tell him they trusted his judgment then, and that at the time he didn't think it was necessary or important. But Gordo has made up his mind now--he wants to be bar mitzvahed. The ceremony is held with all his family and friends in attendance.
Meanwhile, Mrs. Robinson brings home Matt after she'</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>130</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>1</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Melissa Gould</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34806.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196226</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1682</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34807</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>1</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Steve DeJarnatt</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>First Kiss</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>1</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2002-02-08</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Joe Rokicki|Carly Schroeder|Sebastian Jude|Nicholas E. Barb|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Valentine's Day is approaching and Lizzie and Miranda notice that the love bug seems to have bitten everyone in school except Gordo and themselves. At home she talks about it to Miranda on the phone when the McGuire's paperboy Ronny Jacobs comes to the door to collect. She accuses him of eavesdropping on her; he accuses her of being rude to him. She follows him outside to argue, but it's obvious that there is a big attraction between the two. The next day she tells Miranda there's a boy she likes. Miranda is shocked to hear that it's Ronny, not Ethan, and immediately tells Gordo. The next morning Lizzie rushes out to get the paper--because there's a note from Ronny inside it. At school Lizzie is in full crush mode, talking endlessly about Ronny to Miranda, then Gordo. Miranda thinks Gordo is jealous of Ronny, but he denies it. Later Lizzie and Ronny are having a good time skating together. He asks if she considers themselves boyfriend and girlfriend. Both of them are afraid to say it,</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>203</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Terri Minsky</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34807.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196121</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1683</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34808</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>2</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Savage Steve Holland</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>El Oro de Montezuma (aka El Oro del Diablo)</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>2</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2002-02-22</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Erik Estrada|Shalim|Peter Leal|Raja Fenske|Maria Beck|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Lizzie, Miranda and Gordo are vegged out in front of the TV watching a Spanish-language game show, &quot;&quot;El Oro de Montezuma&quot;&quot; (&quot;&quot;The Gold of Montezuma&quot;&quot;). Miranda's cousin Carlos from Mexico City is scheduled to come to town and compete on the show. At school, a new Indonesian student, Li, is introduced to Lizzie's class. She tries to talk to him but finds it difficult since his English is limited. Mr. Dig assigns the students a paper to write on a culture other than their own. Lizzie asks her parents about her heritage, but they aren't very specific. Miranda introduces Carlos to Lizzie and Gordo. When they find out that his teammates for the game show will be unable to appear, Lizzie suggests that the three of them team up with Carlos and go on the show. Lizzie is not very concerned about learning the language, but would rather practice the games and stunts. Meanwhile, Matt and Lanny are involved in an extreme version of hide-and-seek.
The game show begins, and Carlos translates for his team</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>204</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Douglas Tuber|Tim Maile|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34808.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196148</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1683</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34809</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>3</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Steve DeJarnatt</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Mom's Best Friend</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>3</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2002-03-08</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Michael Mantell|Dyana Ortelli|Jeremy J. Bargiel|David Alex Rosen|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Mr. Dig assigns Lizzie a report on a book about a mother-daughter relationship. Lizzie loves the book and decides that she and her mom should become closer friends. Jo McGuire goes along with it and Gordo and Miranda are surprised when Lizzie brings her mom to the Digital Bean to &quot;&quot;hang out!&quot;&quot; Mother and daughter are enjoying their new relationship until Jo confides in Lizzie about some problems she was unaware of: Nana and Grandpa Chuck are having marital troubles and her dad was once in some tax trouble (he was mistaken for Bill Gates and supposedly owed the government $618 million!) All of a sudden Lizzie knows more than she wants to.
Miranda and Gordo decide to follow Lizzie's example and get closer to their parents. Lizzie starts to avoid her mom a little bit, but Jo tracks her down and tells her that Nana and her grandpa worked out their problems. Lizzie admits that she was freaked out by some of the things her mom told her. Jo apologizes and they both decide that maybe they should</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>205</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Douglas Tuber|Tim Maile|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34809.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196052</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1683</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34810</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>4</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director></Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>The Rise and Fall of Kate (aka The Rise and Fall of the Kate Empire)</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>4</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2002-03-15</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars></GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>At lunch, Gordo tries to get seats at the cheerleaders' table for Lizzie, Miranda and himself, but Kate and Claire run them off and they have to eat on the grass. What's worse, they have to watch the cheeleaders practice. While doing a pyramid formation, Kate falls off the top and dislocates her shoulder. The next day when she arrives at the lunch table with her arm in a sling, Claire coldly informs her that since she can't cheer, she's been voted off the squad and isn't allowed to sit with them. All of a sudden Kate is a social nobody, reduced to eating her lunch alone on the grass and banished to the &quot;&quot;dork hall!&quot;&quot;
Lizzie, Miranda and Gordo soon find out that life with Claire as the new &quot;&quot;Queen B&quot;&quot; at the school is much worse that it was with Kate at the top, so Lizzie convinces her friends to start a campaign to make Kate popular again. Their efforts don't work at first, so Lizzie tries another idea: make it possible for Kate to cheer once more. After convincing Kate to go along with th</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>206</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Nina G. Bargiel|Jeremy J. Bargiel|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34810.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1358604248</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1683</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34811</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>5</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Anson Williams</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Working Girl</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>5</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2002-03-29</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Carly Schroeder|Keili Lefkovitz|Nicholas E. Barb|Brian Kimmet|Tom Mastrantonio|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Lizzie is getting tired of running to her parents every time she wants something, but they won't raise her allowance like she asks. So she finds another solution to make her &quot;&quot;free and independent&quot;&quot;--she takes a job as a busboy at the Digital Bean. But the new job is more than she bargained for. Her boss is a tough taskmaster, and rude, obnoxious customers--including Kate and Claire--are running her ragged. Lizzie's dad tells her she doesn't have to keep the job if it is too much trouble, but Lizzie insists it's what she wants to do. But the pressures become too much one day and Lizzie goes ballistic, bawling out her rude customers and slave-driving boss. But her tirade gets her fired!
Meanwhile, Matt laments to his friend Reggie that Melina doesn't care for him anymore--she's found another guy to get in trouble besides him! Reggie suggests he talk to another girl about it. Since Lizzie is too busy these days, Matt goes to Miranda for advice. But when she offers a sympathetic ear and tel</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>210</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Nina G. Bargiel|Jeremy J. Bargiel|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34811.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196100</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1683</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34812</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>6</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Peter Montgomery</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>And the Winner Is</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>6</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2002-04-26</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>Clayton Snyder</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Lizzie, Miranda and Gordo walk into Mr. Dig's class all mad at each other about some incident. Mr. Dig assigns them an historical scavenger hunt in place of a regular test. The former friends find new partners for the hunt: Lizzie latches onto Ethan Craft, Gordo reluctantly teams with Kate Sanders, while Miranda gets stuck with Larry Tudgeman. The trio of teams proceed to search the city for clues that Mr. Dig has left, and the first team to complete the task receives an &quot;&quot;A.&quot;&quot; When Matt finds the assignment in Lizzie's room, he reads that there is &quot;&quot;treasure&quot;&quot; at the end of the search, so he goes off hunting down clues himself. But Mr. Dig's idea of treasure is not the same as Matt's. Meanwhile, Sam and Jo McGuire realize that they have the house to themselves for a while! So what do they naturally do? Act like kids by having pillow fights, eating messy snacks, etc!
While they are on the hunt, Lizzie, Miranda and Gordo reveal to their partners what the big fight with their friends was all</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>211</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Melissa Gould</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34812.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196023</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1683</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34813</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>7</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Steve DeJarnatt</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>The Longest Yard</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>7</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2002-05-17</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Jeremy J. Bargiel|David Alex Rosen|Sean Sweeney|Daniel Chodos|Damien Leake|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Jo McGuire gets roped into attending the Super Sports Expo with her husband, so she makes Lizzie cancel her plans for the day to stay home and watch Matt (and Lanny.) This infuriates Lizzie, but she tries to be responsible and stops the boys from playing with her dad's prize possession, a football autographed by the legendary Walter Payton. But Matt and Lanny managed to deflate the football anyway. Lizzie and Matt know they're in BIG trouble if they can't get the ball fixed, so Lizzie calls Miranda and Gordo over to help her come up with a solution to the problem.
Soon Lizzie has an ever bigger problem. The two young boys have gone off by themselves to try and get the ball fixed. Mrs. McGuire calls to say they will be late arriving home, but she suspects something is wrong when she talks to Lizzie, so Sam asks a couple of his softball buddies to go by the house and check on things. Lizzie and Miranda go off to find Matt and Lanny while Gordo waits at the McGuire house. At first he is h</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>213</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Nina G. Bargiel|Jeremy J. Bargiel|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34813.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196345</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1683</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34814</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>8</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Mark Rosman</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Just Friends</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>8</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2002-06-14</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Christian Copelin|Jake Blakey|Jacob Price|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Gordo encourages Lizzie to finally do something about her crush on Ethan Craft; that is, ask him to the Sadie Hawkins Day dance. But when Lizzie does this she's disappointed when Ethan tells her that he likes their relationship as friends and doesn't want to risk changing it by going out with her. Lizzie is determined to turn herself into a girl who is perfect for Ethan and with the help of Gordo, she begins a surveillance campaign to determine all of Ethan's likes and dislikes so she can make herself over for him. Meanwhile, Matt and Lanny are trying to whip up an &quot;&quot;evil potion,&quot;&quot; but instead they come up with a great-tasting smoothie. It's so good that when they begin to sell it to neighboring kids, Matt's back yard becomes the newest hot spot in town, and soon everyone is flocking to the &quot;&quot;Club Flamingo.&quot;&quot;
Lizzie goes on her campaign for Ethan and it seems to be working: he's knocked out that all of a sudden they seem to have so much in common. She even knows how to dress like his fanta</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>218</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Douglas Tuber|Tim Maile|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34814.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196460</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1683</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34815</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>9</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Oz Scott</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Those Freaky McGuires</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>9</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2002-06-28</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Matteo Crismani|Carly Schroeder|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>As usual, Lizzie and her brother Matt are involved in a big fight. &quot;&quot;Fine! I'll stay out of your life!&quot;&quot; they both scream at each other simultaneously. Then, to their amazement, something totally unbelieveable and mysterious happens--their personalities switch bodies, Matt becoming Lizzie and Lizzie becoming Matt! The siblings are horrified by the change, but they are unable to explain it to their parents, so they have no choice but to go to school like everything was normal. Well, not exactly. Matt (as Lizzie) dresses up like Elton John on his worst day and goes around school tripping over his (her) shoes, making better friends with Ethan Craft by talking about guy stuff like scabs and bruises. Gordo and Miranda are mystified by the changes in the girl they think is their old friend Lizzie, especailly after she pulls a revenge prank on Kate. Meanwhile Lizzie (as Matt) slicks her (his) hair down and dresses like a nerd, hoping to stay quiet and attract as little attention as possible. Bu</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>214</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Melissa Gould</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34815.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196240</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1683</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34816</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>10</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Alan Cohn</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>In Miranda Lizzie Does Not Trust</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>10</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2002-07-05</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Candy Brown Houston|Greg Baker|Cassie Walker|Evan Lee Dahl|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Mr. Dig is teaching dance in gym class, including the &quot;&quot;trust&quot;&quot; exercise, in which one partner (Miranda) falls blindly into the arms of the other (Lizzie). (Gordo has his hands full catching his partner, a ballet-dancing student named Beth, who's about eight inches taller than him!) Later the three friends go shopping. In a department store, Lizzie and Gordo are surprised to see Miranda shovel several handfuls of complimentary candy into her purse. This also draws the attention of the security guard. Later Miranda accidentally bumps into a lipstick display, upsetting the contents. She hurriedly puts things right, then tells Lizzie and Gordo she wants to leave. But the security guard stops her and wants to check her purse. Inside he finds a brand of lipstick from the display. Miranda protests that she bought it at the store last week and asks Lizzie to back her up. But Lizzie says she wasn't there when lipstick was purchased, and the guard takes Miranda away.
Later from her house Miranda</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>212</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Douglas Tuber|Tim Maile|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34816.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196057</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1683</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34817</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>11</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Savage Steve Holland</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Over the Hill</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>11</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2002-07-12</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Carly Schroeder|Anastasia Baranova|Grayce Wey|Brad Grunberg|Jeremy J. Bargiel|David Alex Rosen|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Lizzie starts feeling inferior when she realizes a lot of the other kids around her have special talents and skills that they've developed, including Gordo with his filmmaking and Miranda with her violin. [When did that happen?--Ed.] She worries that she's being left behind and imagines herself in the future working at a fast-food window while her old friends Gordo and Miranda have made successes of themselves and forgotten about her. Lizzie blames her parents at first for not making her pursue a special interest but Sam and Jo McGuire tell her that they've always supported her, whatever she did or didn't do. Finally Lizzie puts a number of &quot;&quot;dream&quot;&quot; occupations in a hat and picks them out one at a time, with Miranda and Gordo on hand. While doing this, Lizzie has fantasies about what her future might be like. The final fantasy is about Lizzie as a stay-home mom, but her husband in it is not Ethan Craft--it's Gordo! This jolts Lizzie back to reality, and she comes to feel OK about hersel</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>207</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Alison Taylor</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34817.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196185</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1683</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34818</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>12</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Tim O'Donnell</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Best Dressed for Much Less (aka Kiss My Budget)</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>12</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2002-07-19</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Timmy Fitzpatrick|John Lowell|Aimee Roldan|Nicholette Dixon|Kelly Vitz|Kate Berlant|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Lizzie wants to win best dressed, but wants to buy really expensive clothes, so her mom goes bargain hunting for clothes instead. </Overview>
  <ProductionCode>217</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Bob Thomas</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34818.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196232</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1683</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34819</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>13</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Peter Montgomery</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>You're a Good Man, Lizzie McGuire</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>13</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2002-07-26</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Phill Lewis|Kathryn Kates|Milana Vayntraub|Katerina Graham|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Lizzie is stuck on the Spring Fling dance committee with Kate. While they are checking out the site for the dance, Kate accidentally knocks over a bust of the school's first principal, cracking the stone head wide open. Kate shows little concern for what she did, though. She thinks if Lizzie keeps quiet, no one will ever know she did it. But Lizzie is concerned about the misdeed. She, Gordo and Miranda try but fail to put the statue back together again--using chewing gum! Principal Tweedy is angry about the &quot;&quot;vandalism&quot;&quot; and announces he will call off the dance if the culprit is not revealed. Gordo warns her not to be &quot;&quot;a fink,&quot;&quot; but Miranda wants Lizzie to tell, because she has a real live date to the dance! Finally, Lizzie goes to see the principal, and at an assembly he announces that Lizzie has confessed to breaking the statue. The dance will be held, but Lizzie will not be allowed to attend. Gordo and Miranda realize what a sacrifice Lizzie just made. Kate is her usual self, telling f</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>216</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Alison Taylor</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34819.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196382</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1683</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34820</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>14</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Anson Williams</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Just Like Lizzie</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>14</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2002-08-09</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Amy Castle|Kenny Lao|Aggi Ghidoni|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Gordo and Miranda may be stressed out about starting the eighth grade, but Lizzie feels great about it. She's so self-confident, in fact, that she's taken on mentoring a seventh-grader named Andie, even though Kate sneers at her for associating with a &quot;&quot;sevy.&quot;&quot; Andie seems to worship the ground that Lizzie walks on, and it appears to be a great arrangement at first. But things start to turn a little creepy when Andie starts turning into a clone of Lizzie, imitating her hair style, then dying her hair, then dressing exactly like her! What's even more unnerving to Lizzie is how much Gordo and Miranda like her--even more than the real item, it seems! Gordo is especially taken with Andie, and he actually talks about dating her!
Meanwhile, Matt faces a crisis with his Wilderness Cadets group. He must earn a merit patch very soon or he will be demoted to a Bunny Cadet! Dad tries to help him earn the patch but only proceeds to get a bad case of poison ivy and nearly sets himself on fire.
Lizzie</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>201</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Melissa Gould</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34820.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196298</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1683</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34821</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>15</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Savage Steve Holland</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Lizzie in the Middle</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>15</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2002-08-23</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Frankie Muniz|Clayton Snyder|Bill LaMond|William Keane|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Lizzie is in class reading lines from Romeo and Juliet with Ethan when an old acquaintance of Mr. Dig's comes in--it's Frankie Muniz, star of Malcolm in the Middle! Frankie is transfixed by Lizzie, and when Miranda comes to lunch, she's surprised to find Lizzie and Gordo sitting there eating with Frankie! After some small talk, Frankie asks Lizzie out. Miranda and Gordo are shocked when Lizzie doesn't answer. She finally says &quot;&quot;I don't know,&quot;&quot; at which point a mob of students descends on Frankie, looking for autographs.
At home Lizzie tells Miranda and Gordo she's not going out with Frankie because they live in &quot;&quot;different worlds.&quot;&quot; Miranda argues that she should get to know him and give him a chance. When Lizzie's parents hear about the situation, they're split: Dad says no way should she date a movie star, Mom says yes. Matt volunteers to head Lizzie's &quot;&quot;entourage&quot;&quot; that she'll need as the girlfriend of someone famous. Frankie comes to the door hoping to convince Lizzie to give him another</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>223</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Nina G. Bargiel|Jeremy J. Bargiel|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34821.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196191</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1683</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34822</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>16</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Mark Rosman</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Inner Beauty</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>16</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2002-08-30</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Christian Copelin|Travis Payne|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Miranda and Lizzie are rehearsing dance steps for a music video Gordo is making. During a break he makes an offhand remark about how much snack food Miranda is putting away. The next day at school Gordo shows the girls some still photos he took the day before. Miranda, already puting pressure on herself to make better grades and improve herself, reacts unreasonably to one picture, saying that she looks terribly fat, even though Lizzie and Gordo assure she's not at all. Later at lunch Miranda, quite unlike herself, doesn't eat anything.  At the McGuire house afterwards, the trio is rehaersing for the video again. Miranda grows faint and almost passes out in front of Mrs. McGuire. Miranda assures everyone that she's alright, but Lizzie is still concerned. When Lizzie tries to talk to her later, Miranda is very unresponsive and uncooperative.
Lizzie talks to her mom about Miranda, saying that she's especially concerned about her new eating habits. Jo McGuire agrees to talk to Miranda and</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>208</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Melissa Gould</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34822.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196326</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1683</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34823</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>17</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Mark Rosman</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Movin' On Up</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>17</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2002-09-13</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Vanessa Sapien|Joy Lauren|Willie Green|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Gordo has received some big news: he has the chance to skip the eighth grade and start high school immediately. When Lizzie and Miranda hear this, they strongly encourage him to do it, saying high school is so much cooler than junior high. But Gordo isn't sure about it, and when he points out that a move to high sachool will split up the trio, the girls all of a sudden have something serious to think about too. Lizzie and Miranda now decide they don't want their best friend leaving them, but they are shocked when they find Gordo cleaning out his locker the next day--he's going to high school. Miranda recovers quickly and wishes him the best, but Lizzie is clearly stunned and her alter ego Toon Lizzie urges her to say something to Gordo to try to make him stay, but she doesn't.
On Gordo's first day at high school, Lizzie is still terribly troubled by his absence. Miranda is more realistic. She'll miss him too, but she knows it's what he wants and it's something that is good for him. For</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>202</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Nina G. Bargiel|Jeremy J. Bargiel|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34823.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196262</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1683</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34824</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>18</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Savage Steve Holland</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Party Over Here</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>18</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2002-09-20</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Zachary Quinto|Audrey Wasilewski|Haylie Duff|Rachelle Carson|Cory Hodges|Shad Sager|Josh Martinez|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Kate is having a big birthday party and her mother is making her invite her whole class, including Lizzie, Miranda and Gordo. Lizzie is dead set against going until she finds out cell phones will be given out as party favors. But her mom puts the brakes on her idea of going because there will be no &quot;&quot;acceptable chaperone&quot;&quot; there. Miranda suggests the three of them say they are going to the mall, then sneak out to the party. Lizzie is reluctant to go along with the idea, but she does. Gordo gets his parents' permission to go, but that only frustrates him since his parents think he's such a good boy he couldn't possibly get into trouble. So he tries, rather unsuccessfully, to show he has a dangerous &quot;&quot;dark side.&quot;&quot;
When Lizzie, Miranda and Gordo arrive at Kate's house the party is ragin': loud music is pumping, Lizzie gets handed over people's heads like a stage diver in a mosh pit, and the supposed &quot;&quot;chaperone,&quot;&quot; Kate's 18-year-old cousin Amy, is making out in the closet! None of their classma</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>209</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Alison Taylor</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34824.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196218</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1683</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34825</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>19</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Brian K. Roberts</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>She Said, He Said, She Said</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>19</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2002-11-22</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Christian Copelin|Phill Lewis|Marissa Leigh|Taylor Hoover|Josh Strode|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>A major food fight is raging in the cafeteria. Lizzie, Gordo and Miranda try to stay on the sidelines until Lizzie gets hit squarely with a meatball. In anger she grabs another one herself, cocks her arm and yells &quot;&quot;Who threw that?!?!&quot;&quot; Unfortunately, that's the moment when Principal Tweedy walks in the door. He sees Lizzie, Kate Sanders and Larry Tudgeman right in the middle of things and calls them to his office. For punishment, the three will have to clean up the huge mess and do some community service, but they can ease their punishment if they write out an account of what happened and name the person responsible for starting the food fight.
Stuck together working, the trio each tell their own version of how the fight started, shown in flashbacks. In Kate's account, she arrives at school greeted like the queen she thinks she is. She's kind and caring to all her subjects and everyone loves her, including Lizzie, Miranda and Gordo, who are dying to be her friend again. Larry's version</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>222</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Melissa Gould</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34825.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196373</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1683</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34826</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>20</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Savage Steve Holland</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Xtreme Xmas</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>20</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2002-12-06</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Tai Tallirico|Chelsea Tallirico|Jackson Rogow|Troy Rowland|Brad Grunberg|Austin W. Glenn|Samantha Smith|Jeremy J. Bargiel|David Alex Rosen|Haylie Duff|Steven Tyler|Shelley Berman|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Lizzie and Gordo are at a Christmans charity drive where the bring presents to an unlikely-looking Santa Claus. Lizzie ferventy hopes to win the grand prize in the Christmas parade with her idea for a &quot;&quot;Rock &amp; Roll Christmas&quot;&quot; float, but she'll have competition from Tudgeman, who is building a &quot;&quot;Christmas Deathstar&quot;&quot; float and also Kate and her cousin Amy, who have hired professionals to build theirs. The rest of the McGuire family are there, and they are charmed by an eccentric old man in an elf suit who calls himself Nobby Frostybump and seems to really believe he's one of Santa's elves! Lizzie is disappointed that her family is going off to dinner with Nobby instead of working on the float, but Gordo stays to help. Hours later, Lizzie comes home and is surprised by Nobby. His senior-citizens home is having plumbing problems and he will stay with the McGuires fro a few days.
The next day Lizzie and Gordo are busy working on the float. Nobby gets the bad news that the plumbing in his buil</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>233</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Douglas Tuber|Tim Maile|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34826.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196163</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1683</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34827</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>21</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Robert Carradine</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Lizzie's Eleven</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>21</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2003-01-01</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Kenneth Schmidt|Joey Zimmerman|Troy Rowland|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Lizzie is doing some awfully strange things to get her picture in the class yearbook as many times as possible. When Gordo puts her down for this, she reminds him he did the very same thing himself earlier. Lizzie figures she will be in eleven different pictures, but the yearbook editor Kate has different ideas. True to her usually-rotten self, Kate tells Lizzie she's only going to let a single picture of her run in the yearbook--one in which she's breaking out in a rash from a food allergy! Kate plans to get her picture taken with Ethan at the school's Monte Carlo Night that evening, then rush the yearbook off to the printer. To foil this plan, Lizzie comes up with an elaborate scheme worthy of the casino heist in the movie Ocean's Eleven. The whole McGuire clan gets involved, including Matt, who is persuaded along by a major wedgie given to him by Lizzie! Gordo and Melina also help out on the grand design.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>229</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Douglas Tuber|Tim Maile|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34827.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196311</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1683</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34828</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>22</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Mark Rosman</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Dear Lizzie</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>22</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2003-01-24</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Tonya Rowland|Sean Marquette|Chelsea J. Wilson|Taylor Colman|Mitchah Williams|Simms Thomas|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Gordo, editor of the schools &quot;&quot;E-zine,&quot;&quot; reluctantly makes Lizzie the website's advice columnist (it was either her or the flaky faculty advisor Ms. Dew.) But she does surprisingly well in the job. After giving great advice to students like Parker McKenzie and Claire Miller, Lizzie's reputation and popularity skyrocket. But soon she gets overwhelmed with requests for help, and some of the advice she gives turns out badly, like when she suggests to Veruca that she stand up to the school bully. Now Lizzie's afraid to give help to others who have asked, like Ethan, Kate and Tudgeman. Lizzie imagines the possible bad results of her advice: Ethan cuts off all his hair, Kate joins the Peace Corps and becomes a menu selection for cannibals, and Tudge becomes a &quot;&quot;Dr. Evil&quot;&quot;-like villain demanding two billion dollars from President Craft (and First Lady Kate) or he will destroy the world! Lizzie's confidence is badly shaken and she's ready to quit the job, but Gordo wants her to stay on. He comprom</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>230</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Nina G. Bargiel|Jeremy J. Bargiel|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34828.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196433</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1683</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34829</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>23</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Peter Montgomery</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Clue-Less</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>23</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2003-01-31</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Haylie Duff|Catherine Chiarelli|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>What's this? Lizzie in a wedding dress, walking down the aisle? Gordo, Kate, Tudgeman, Cousin Amy and Veruca are all in the audience, but they're dressed strangely in old fashioned clothes. And now we see that Lizzie's about to marry Ethan!?!? Just before &quot;&quot;I do,&quot;&quot; Jo McGuire comes rushing in wearing a maid's uniform, shouting in a near-incomprehensible  Cockney accent about someone being murdered!! Whaaaa?
Let's go back a few days...
Ethan tells Lizzie that he can't use his own house for a party he had planned, so she volunteers her own house, hoping to get his attention, as always. It's going to be a 1920's murder-mystery party, where all the guests play a character and compete to solve the mystery. When everyone gathers to pick their parts, Lizzie can't believe her luck: she picked Ethan's wife-to-be! Gordo on the other hand is disappointed. He tells Lizzie that once again he'll be the &quot;&quot;low-key&quot;&quot; friend that no one notices. Lizzie assures him that people do notice him, and that one way</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>232</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Douglas Tuber|Tim Maile|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34829.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196447</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1683</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34830</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>24</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Ken Ceizler</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Bye, Bye Hillridge Junior High</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>24</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2003-02-07</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Phill Lewis|Troy Rowland|Mitchah Williams|Rory Shoaf|Sarah Kapp|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Lizzie is excited by the prospect of graduation from junior high and moving on to high school. But when she gets to school she finds a flyer distributed by the high-schoolers warning the junior high kids about what's in store for them when they get on &quot;&quot;their&quot;&quot; territory. Yearbooks are being distributed also, and along with an insult from Kate, all this makes for a change in Lizzie's attitude. She starts thinking that she's been a failure in junior high and will be a nobody in high school. Her reliable friend Gordo tries to assure her that neither is true. Lizzie jokes about preparing to write, &quot;&quot;You rock, don't ever change&quot;&quot; a hundred times in yearbooks. While looking through the book, Lizzie and Gordo share tons of memories, illustrated throughout the show by film clips and still photos from many of the previous episodes. Larry Tudgeman asks Lizzie to sign his book and Lizzie writes a very sweet message referring to the times they had together. She tells Gordo that Tudge was the ony boy</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>234</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Jaime Becker</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34830.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196268</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1683</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34831</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>25</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Anson Williams</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Bunkies</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>25</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2003-02-21</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Lamont Thompson|Deance Wyatt|Kimberly Aaberg|Nick Huff|Simms Thomas|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>A water pipe bursts in a wall in Matt's room and to Lizzie's horror she'll have to share her room with her brother until the repairs are done. That doesn't look like it will be anytime soon, as the McGuires have hired a repairman who could have come straight out of the movie The Money Pit. Predictably, the pairing of Matt and Lizzie doesn't work at all. They fight about everything--he wants the window open, she wants it closed; she wants the shade down, he wants it up; he wants the door closed, she wants it open. All the bickering keeps Mr. McGuire, already frazzled by the repairman, awake all night.
Lizzie's not doing too good at school, either. The spacey art teacher Ms. Dew has come up with an idea for a school &quot;&quot;unity&quot;&quot; project: all the students will dip their hands in paint and put their handprints on a blank wall, making a mural. But instead of promoting unity, the students break into cliques, and Lizzie, Miranda and Gordo don't fit into any of them, not Kate and the cheerleaders,</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>220</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Bob Thomas</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34831.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196128</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1683</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34832</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>26</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Savage Steve Holland</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>A Gordo Story (aka Inner Beauty II: A Gordo Story)</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>26</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2003-02-28</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Christian Copelin|Chelsea J. Wilson|Tricia Cruz|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Lizzie, Gordo, Miranda and Ethan Craft are playing a little basketball (and doing a lot of trash-talkin'!) when Parker McKenzie comes by to watch. After Gordo gets his last shot stuffed by Ethan, Parker comes over to talk, and it looks like she's got her eye on Gordo. He surprises Lizzie and Miranda by saying he might ask Parker out to the upcoming dance. Later at the Digital Bean, though, he's hesitating until Lizzie and Miranda encourage him to do it. When he does ask Parker, she simply tells him, &quot;&quot;I can't.&quot;&quot; Lizzie asks her why she turned Gordo down and Parker is blunt: he's short. He might be a nice enough guy to hang out with, but she doesn't want to go out with a short guy. Gordo overhears this and is obviously devastated. He leave the Digital Bean, leaving behind his two friends, who don't feel very good, either.
At school the next day, Lizzie and Miranda are still concerned. Gordo stumbles onto the scene wearing a pair of new (high-heeled) cowboy boots, claiming he's OK with wha</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>215</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Jeremy J. Bargiel|Nina G. Bargiel|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34832.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196015</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1683</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34833</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>27</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Steve DeJarnatt</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Grubby Longjohn's Olde Tyme Revue</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>27</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2003-03-14</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Joseph Whipp|Haley Hudson|Josh Wise|Jack Barrett Phelan|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>The McGuire family members are all psyched about making their annual journey to Grubby Gulch, a &quot;&quot;Wild West&quot;&quot; theme park, after missing last year's trip. That is, all except Lizzie, who feels that she's too old for such a &quot;&quot;lame&quot;&quot; place. But at least she has Miranda and Gordo going with her--although neither of them realize how much they too will dislike the place or that they'll have to get up at 5:30AM for the six-hour trip there!
Once they arrive at Grubby Gulch and are greeted by Grubby Longjohn himself, Mr. and Mrs. McGuire and Matt couldn't be happier, but the place is as lame and embarrassing as Lizzie had remembered it, and Gordo and Miranda agree with her. But there is one bright spot. At a concession stand, Lizzie strikes up an acquaintance with a cute boy, Cory, and Gordo meets a nice-looking girl, Clementine. They invite Lizzie and Gordo to go to the mall with them after work, and they even have a date for Miranda. But it turns out that Mr. McGuire has scored some hard-to-get t</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>219</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Douglas Tuber|Tim Maile|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34833.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196080</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1683</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34834</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>28</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Rachel Feldman</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>The Greatest Crush of All (aka My Love Is a Red Red Chimp)</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>28</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2003-03-21</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Grant Thompson|Jeremy J. Bargiel|David Alex Rosen|Lee Everett|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Lizzie and Miranda's new English teacher Mr. Keith is really from England--and really cute, too! All the girls are ga-ga from the minute they see him, and once he starts teaching them about the love poetry of Robert Burns, they're all under his spell. (Even Gordo and Tudge like him after he tells them how much girls go for this poetry stuff.) Lizzie decides she wants to be the one girl that Mr. Keith notices, so she begins talking with him and bringing him little presents. But this puts her in direct conflict with her best friend Miranda, who's doing the same thing, not to mention other girls too, like Kate and Veruca.
Meanwhile at home, the McGuires get a surprise--Dad has neglected to tell the rest of the family that they'll be keeping Fredo the chimp for a week while his owners are out of town. When Fredo arrives, Matt is very wary--he remembers how much trouble the chimp got him in once before. But soon Matt starts taking kindly to Fredo, and he becomes almost like a brother! Lizzi</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>224</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Douglas Tuber|Tim Maile|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34834.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196291</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1683</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34835</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>29</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Savage Steve Holland</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Grand Ole Grandma</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>29</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2003-04-04</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>Doris Roberts</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Gordo is looking forward to the arrival of a favorite relative, his Grandma Ruth, who is coming for a week while his parents are away. But when he takes Lizzie and Miranda over to his house to greet her after her arrival, he's thrown for a loop. Grandma is dressing differently in &quot;&quot;spicy&quot;&quot; outfits and going by the name &quot;&quot;Gorgeous!&quot;&quot; She's not making brisket and kugel for him anymore, she's serving sushi and whole meals made of appetizers. And she's into--parachuting?!
The next morning at the McGuire house something odd happens--Lizzie and Matt are up and ready before Mom and Dad have gotten out of bed. But the parents soon stumble downstairs and it's obvious they are both sick with some kind of bug; in fact, the fever is putting both of them a little on the delirious side! They go back to bed, hand the kids some money for pizza and tell them they'll have to take care of themselves for a while. Matt and Lizzie prepare to enjoy themselves.
Gordo comes home to find that Ruth has &quot;&quot;feng shue&quot;&quot;'d</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>226</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Melissa Gould</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34835.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196467</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1683</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34836</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>30</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Mark Rosman</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>My Fair Larry</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>30</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2003-05-16</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Dabbs Greer|Eileen Brennan|Tonya Rowland|Kathryn Kates|Dan Swett|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Miranda is psyched about being allowed to have a real &quot;&quot;boy/girl&quot;&quot; party at her place. She wants to make it the coolest party ever, so she invites Kate, Ethan, and everyone else--except Larry Tudgeman. Lizzie thinks this is unkind to Tudgeman, but Miranda is sure he will only ruin the party. After Miranda hands invitations out to everyone, Larry comes up and asks where his is; she tells him his not invited, she didn't think he'd be interested. Tudge is obviously hurt but tries to act like he has other things to do, namely a Star Trek &quot;&quot;Star Fleet&quot;&quot; convention to attend. Lizzie feels so sorry for Larry that she devises a plan and enlists the help of Gordo after reminding him how upset he felt when Danny Kessler didn't invite him to his pool party. They convince Larry to let them help him and turn him from uncool Larry into very stylish Lawrence (after a few makeovers that don't work so well!). After sneaking him into the party everyone wants to know who this new guy is, even Kate! Miranda i</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>227</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Jeremy J. Bargiel|Nina G. Bargiel|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34836.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196245</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1683</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34837</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>31</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Steve DeJarnatt</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>The Gordo Shuffle</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>31</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2003-06-13</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Ricky Luna|Brian J. White|Troy Rowland|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>At school, Gordo tells Lizzie and Ethan he got a credit card in the mail with a $5,000 line of credit. He says he's not going to keep it, but the other two convince him to hang onto it. Later, though, while talking to Lizzie on the phone, Gordo has a brainstorm: use the credit card to finance the film he wants to make! Later at school Gordo is in full director mode, hiring Tudgeman as his technical advisor and Ethan and Kate as the leads in his science-fiction flick. He even hires Claire as Kate's personal stylist, then gives the two girls the card to go spend on wardrobe and make-up! Lizzie watches all this and is very concerned with the way Gordo is throwing around money that he doesn't really have. When she tells him this, he gets mad at her for not being supportive of his lifelong dream of filmmaking.
When filming actually begins, nothing goes right. Kate, not surprisingly, acts like a prima donna, Ethan can't get his lines straight and Gordo can't seem to get a single good take to</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>231</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Melissa Gould</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34837.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196396</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1683</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34838</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>32</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Rusty Russ</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>My Dinner with Dig</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>32</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2003-08-15</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Carly Schreoder|Tonya Rowland|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>Lizzie is in a tizzy--she casually mentions to Mr. Dig at lunch one day that he should eat more home-cooked, well-balanced meals, and somehow she ends up inviting him to dinner! She's in a panic at the idea of having to deal with a teacher outside of school, and sure enough the dinner with Mr. Dig starts out disastrously. But the next day at school she tells Gordo and Miranda that the evening actually turned out well. As a matter of fact her father Sam and &quot;&quot;Digby&quot;&quot; seem to have struck up a friendship. Her mind changes, though, when to her horror, her dad actually shows up at school to exchange CD's with his new buddy!
Meanwhile Matt has his own problems. He, Melina and his classmates are all being terrorized by their teacher Ms. Chapman, who seems to always be in a bad mood of late. Matt and Melina decide that she needs to get a life outside of the classroom to make her a more relaxed person, so to that end Matt invites her over for dinner at his house one evening.
Lizzie is freaked out</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>228</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>Melissa Gould</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34838.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196410</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1683</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34839</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>33</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Steve DeJarnatt</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>One of the Guys</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>33</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2003-11-21</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Julian Jackson|Tonya Rowland|Andrew McFarlane|Dot Jones|Jeremy J. Bargiel|Phillip Blackwell|David Alex Rosen|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>After setting a new school record in gym and then beating Ethan Craft in arm-wrestling, Lizzie is invited to play touch football with the &quot;&quot;cute guys.&quot;&quot; But after winning the game, Ethan and the guys call her a &quot;&quot;great dude&quot;&quot; and &quot;&quot;a monster&quot;&quot; while Kate insults her as a &quot;&quot;guy-girl.&quot;&quot; This worries Lizzie so much that she makes an early-morning call to Miranda for advice. Miranda suggests she emphasize her feminine side more, which Lizzie spends the rest of the morning doing. A talk with Coach Kelly helps Lizzie see things in a different light. Afterward she tells off Kate and goes back onto the field to play with the boys again.
Meanwhile, Matt isn't doing his math homework. He falls asleep and wakes up to find it all done, but he has no idea that Fredo the chimp snuck into his room and did it for him! Before the truth comes out, Jo and Sam are happy to see their son doing so well in the subject and Melina wants Matt to do her homework for her.</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>225</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Nina G. Bargiel|Jeremy J. Bargiel|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34839.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196441</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1683</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
<Episode>
  <id>34840</id>
  <Combined_episodenumber>34</Combined_episodenumber>
  <Combined_season>2</Combined_season>
  <DVD_chapter></DVD_chapter>
  <DVD_discid></DVD_discid>
  <DVD_episodenumber></DVD_episodenumber>
  <DVD_season></DVD_season>
  <Director>Henry Chan</Director>
  <EpImgFlag>1</EpImgFlag>
  <EpisodeName>Magic Train (aka Lizzie and Miranda's Magic Train)</EpisodeName>
  <EpisodeNumber>34</EpisodeNumber>
  <FirstAired>2004-02-14</FirstAired>
  <GuestStars>|Lyle Kanouse|Prince Daivdson|Michael Krepack|Ronit Mann|Sandy Fox|</GuestStars>
  <IMDB_ID></IMDB_ID>
  <Language>en</Language>
  <Overview>One day after school Lizzie and Miranda are working on their makeup when they happen to see an old childhood favorite &quot;&quot;Clover and Daisy's Magic Train&quot;&quot; on TV. At first both try to dismiss any interest in the &quot;&quot;kiddie&quot;&quot; program but finally admit it's still one of their favorites. When Lizzie and Miranda discover that it will be in their town they decide it would be fun to attend a taping of the show. But there's a problem, what would people think of two teenagers attending a children's program? Their solution is to find a child who wants to see the program and they can baby-sit.   Lizzie and Miranda's first option is Matt, but he's too old for such a baby show and quickly turns them down because he's working on &quot;&quot;The McGuire Museum of Dirt, Stains and Grime.&quot;&quot; Next they try to get Gordo's four year old cousin, Taylor, but his family has moved out of town, so things are looking hopeless. Gordo asks what do they need a young child for so Lizzie and Miranda tell him about Clover and Daisy. Gord</Overview>
  <ProductionCode>221</ProductionCode>
  <Rating></Rating>
  <RatingCount>0</RatingCount>
  <SeasonNumber>2</SeasonNumber>
  <Writer>|Wendy Engelberg|Amy Engelberg|</Writer>
  <absolute_number></absolute_number>
  <filename>episodes/71119/34840.jpg</filename>
  <lastupdated>1431196177</lastupdated>
  <seasonid>1683</seasonid>
  <seriesid>71119</seriesid>
  <thumb_added></thumb_added>
  <thumb_height>300</thumb_height>
  <thumb_width>400</thumb_width>
</Episode>
</Data>